1
00:00:44,540 --> 00:00:47,960
Excuse me.Could you tell me how to get to the medical school?

2
00:00:48,130 --> 00:00:51,800
I'm supposed to be doing a lecture in 20 minutes, and my driver's a bit lost.

3
00:00:53,300 --> 00:00:58,300
You go straight ahead and you make a left over the bridge.

4
00:01:00,140 --> 00:01:02,310
That's a lovely accent you have.

5
00:01:02,470 --> 00:01:04,220
New Jersey?

6
00:01:04,390 --> 00:01:05,640
Austria.

7
00:01:05,810 --> 00:01:07,520
Austria?

8
00:01:07,690 --> 00:01:09,150
well, then...

9
00:01:09,310 --> 00:01:11,150
good day, mate.

10
00:01:12,150 --> 00:01:15,610
Let's put another shrimp on the barbie.

11
00:01:16,200 --> 00:01:18,320
Let's not.

12
00:02:10,060 --> 00:02:11,930


13
00:02:41,530 --> 00:02:44,240
who's got the wiener schnitzel?

14
00:02:45,410 --> 00:02:46,910
Beautiful. There you go, Dolf.

15
00:02:47,080 --> 00:02:49,330
There you go, buddy. Yeah, enjoy.

16
00:02:50,420 --> 00:02:54,840
Let's see, next we got roast beef au jus.

17
00:02:55,420 --> 00:02:57,210
who's got the roast beef au jus?

18
00:02:57,380 --> 00:02:59,420
Stella, beautiful. Bon appetit, Stella.

19
00:03:00,760 --> 00:03:03,300
Yeah, walk away. Go on, go on.

20
00:03:03,800 --> 00:03:06,260
Last but not least, footlong.

21
00:03:06,430 --> 00:03:09,220
who's got the footlong?

22
00:03:09,390 --> 00:03:11,890
Very...Very funny, Rascal.

23
00:03:12,060 --> 00:03:13,600
Very funny. In your dreams.

24
00:03:13,770 --> 00:03:17,440
Harry, why haven't you dropped those dogs off at the show yet?

25
00:03:17,610 --> 00:03:21,650
Sir, I didn't want to send them to a performance on an empty stomach, sir.

26
00:03:21,820 --> 00:03:23,030
Get a move on it.

27
00:03:23,200 --> 00:03:26,370
Yes, sir. Mutt Cutts. Ten-four.

28
00:03:47,390 --> 00:03:49,140
Suck me sideways.

29
00:04:02,400 --> 00:04:04,860
Hello.How are you?

30
00:04:11,660 --> 00:04:14,370
-I'll be out in one minute. -Okay.

31
00:04:42,860 --> 00:04:44,650
why you going to the airport?

32
00:04:44,820 --> 00:04:46,820
Flying somewhere?

33
00:04:47,280 --> 00:04:50,160
-How'd you guess? -well, I saw your luggage.

34
00:04:50,330 --> 00:04:53,540
Then when I noticed the airline ticket, I put two and two together.

35
00:04:54,370 --> 00:04:57,170
-So where you headed? -Aspen.

36
00:04:57,630 --> 00:05:01,170
Mm. California. Beautiful.

37
00:05:04,010 --> 00:05:06,880
Name's Christmas, Lloyd Christmas.

38
00:05:07,550 --> 00:05:09,220
I'm Mary Swanson.

39
00:05:10,310 --> 00:05:12,220
This isn't my real job, you know.

40
00:05:12,390 --> 00:05:13,560
-No? -Nope.

41
00:05:13,730 --> 00:05:17,350
My friend Harry and I are saving up our money to open our own pet store.

42
00:05:17,520 --> 00:05:18,560
That's nice.

43
00:05:19,860 --> 00:05:21,360
I Got worms.

44
00:05:22,030 --> 00:05:24,780
-I beg your pardon? -That's what we're gonna call it.

45
00:05:24,940 --> 00:05:28,410
I Got worms. we're gonna specialize in selling worm farms.

46
00:05:28,570 --> 00:05:30,570
You know, like ant farms?

47
00:05:32,240 --> 00:05:34,240
what's the matter?

48
00:05:34,750 --> 00:05:36,500
A little tense about the flight?

49
00:05:37,920 --> 00:05:39,750
Something like that.

50
00:05:40,420 --> 00:05:42,340
There's really nothing to worry about.

51
00:05:42,500 --> 00:05:45,920
Statistically, you're more likely to get killed on the way to the airport.

52
00:05:46,090 --> 00:05:50,220
Like in a head-on crash or flying off a cliff or getting trapped under a gas truck.

53
00:05:50,390 --> 00:05:51,390
That's the worst.

54
00:05:52,720 --> 00:05:54,560
I have this cousin...well, I had this cousin. He's like, pbbt...

55
00:05:55,980 --> 00:05:58,190
Lloyd, could you keep your eyes on the road, please?

56
00:05:58,770 --> 00:06:00,480
Oh, yeah.

57
00:06:00,810 --> 00:06:02,150
Good thinking.

58
00:06:02,320 --> 00:06:03,650
Can't be too careful.

59
00:06:03,820 --> 00:06:05,940
Lot of bad drivers out there.

60
00:06:13,410 --> 00:06:14,620
Hey, watch it!

61
00:06:23,090 --> 00:06:24,880
Okay, gang. You know the rules.

62
00:06:25,050 --> 00:06:27,420
No humping, no pushing, no sniffing heinies.

63
00:06:27,590 --> 00:06:28,800
where have you been?

64
00:06:28,970 --> 00:06:31,470
My dogs were supposed to be here 40 minutes ago.

65
00:06:31,640 --> 00:06:33,890
Now, I hardly have any time to primp them.

66
00:06:34,060 --> 00:06:36,350
Don't worry about a thing, Mrs. Neugyburger.

67
00:06:36,520 --> 00:06:38,430
-Neugeboren. -Neu...Neu...Neu...

68
00:06:38,600 --> 00:06:40,060
-Boren. -Boren. These pooches...

69
00:06:40,230 --> 00:06:43,650
are not gonna need primping. You know why? Because I bathed them...

70
00:06:43,820 --> 00:06:45,270
and I clipped them myself.

71
00:06:45,440 --> 00:06:48,190
And I stand by my performance.

72
00:06:59,330 --> 00:07:02,170
On second thought, you might wanna run a comb through them.

73
00:07:02,460 --> 00:07:04,460
The white zone is for...

74
00:07:04,630 --> 00:07:07,340
the immediate loading and unloading of passengers only.

75
00:07:07,510 --> 00:07:09,090
No parking.

76
00:07:11,300 --> 00:07:15,760
-Thanks. Here you go. -Oh, no, Mary.

77
00:07:16,430 --> 00:07:18,310
I couldn't possibly accept that.

78
00:07:18,470 --> 00:07:20,680
Not after all we've been through.

79
00:07:23,860 --> 00:07:26,110
Thank you, Lloyd.

80
00:07:26,440 --> 00:07:29,150
-Good luck with your worms. -Thanks.

81
00:07:32,530 --> 00:07:34,030
How about a hug?

82
00:07:34,200 --> 00:07:39,120
The white zone is for the immediate loading and unloading of passengers only.

83
00:07:39,290 --> 00:07:40,830
No parking.

84
00:07:50,880 --> 00:07:53,380
I hate goodbyes.

85
00:08:00,560 --> 00:08:02,890
-Uh, Lloyd... -Shh.

86
00:08:04,020 --> 00:08:05,810
Just go.

87
00:08:27,500 --> 00:08:30,130
Be strong.

88
00:08:43,890 --> 00:08:47,690
Mr. Dan Richard, please pick up the white courtesy phone.

89
00:08:47,860 --> 00:08:52,730
Mr.Dan Richard, please pick up the white courtesy phone.

90
00:08:52,900 --> 00:08:55,740
She's gonna leave the briefcase near the escalator.

91
00:08:55,910 --> 00:08:59,530
-You make the pickup. -Piece of cake.

92
00:09:07,960 --> 00:09:09,460
Goodbye, my love

93
00:09:16,720 --> 00:09:18,130
Bye.

94
00:09:19,350 --> 00:09:23,560
passenger warren passion, please pick up the white courtesy phone.

95
00:09:23,720 --> 00:09:25,100
You have a message.

96
00:09:25,270 --> 00:09:27,270
passenger warren passion....

97
00:09:34,150 --> 00:09:35,400
Mary!

98
00:09:37,280 --> 00:09:39,320
There's our payday.

99
00:09:40,830 --> 00:09:43,740
-She left it. Let's go. -Excuse me.

100
00:09:43,910 --> 00:09:46,000
Coming through.

101
00:09:48,120 --> 00:09:50,580
Move it or lose it, sister.

102
00:10:12,570 --> 00:10:14,400
Hold that plane!

103
00:10:14,570 --> 00:10:16,610
Sir, you can't go in there.

104
00:10:16,780 --> 00:10:18,490
It's okay.

105
00:10:18,650 --> 00:10:20,990
I'm a limo driver.

106
00:10:49,480 --> 00:10:51,900
-Hi, Lloyd. -Hi, Harry.

107
00:10:52,900 --> 00:10:54,060
How was your day?

108
00:10:54,230 --> 00:10:57,030
Not bad. Fell off the Jetway again.

109
00:11:03,740 --> 00:11:06,910
who the hell do you figure this guy's working for, anyway?

110
00:11:07,240 --> 00:11:08,870
I don't know...

111
00:11:10,620 --> 00:11:13,210
but we sure as hell better find out.

112
00:11:17,710 --> 00:11:20,880
-The ulcer? -I'll live.

113
00:11:29,060 --> 00:11:32,020
-So you got fired again, huh? -Oh, yeah.

114
00:11:32,770 --> 00:11:36,310
They always freak out when you leave the scene of an accident, you know?

115
00:11:37,900 --> 00:11:40,280
Yeah, well, I lost my job too.

116
00:11:41,110 --> 00:11:45,950
Man, you are one pathetic loser.

117
00:11:47,120 --> 00:11:50,040
-No offense. -No. None taken.

118
00:11:55,130 --> 00:11:57,460
You know what really chaffs my ass, though?

119
00:11:57,630 --> 00:12:01,130
I spent my life savings turning my van into a dog.

120
00:12:01,720 --> 00:12:02,970
Hi, Petey.

121
00:12:03,130 --> 00:12:06,800
-The alarm alone cost me 200. -Hey, chicks love it.

122
00:12:06,970 --> 00:12:08,930
It's a shagging wagon.

123
00:12:10,140 --> 00:12:12,140
what's with the briefcase?

124
00:12:15,940 --> 00:12:17,310
It's a love memento.

125
00:12:17,480 --> 00:12:20,320
The most beautiful woman alive.

126
00:12:20,610 --> 00:12:25,860
I drove her to the airport, sparks flew, emotions ran high.

127
00:12:26,320 --> 00:12:27,820
She actually talked to me, man.

128
00:12:29,160 --> 00:12:31,870
-Get out of here. -Oh, yeah. Yeah.

129
00:12:32,040 --> 00:12:33,040
Tractor beam.

130
00:12:34,370 --> 00:12:36,000
Sucked me right in.

131
00:12:36,500 --> 00:12:38,080
Anyway...

132
00:12:39,500 --> 00:12:44,130
she left this in the terminal and flew to Aspen and out of my life.

133
00:12:44,880 --> 00:12:46,510
what's in it?

134
00:12:48,350 --> 00:12:50,890
Man, I would have to be a lowlife...

135
00:12:51,060 --> 00:12:53,850
to go rooting around in somebody else's private property.

136
00:12:54,020 --> 00:12:55,020
ls it locked?

137
00:12:55,190 --> 00:12:57,350
Yeah, really well.

138
00:13:05,700 --> 00:13:08,240
There's two of them. One of them's got a gun.

139
00:13:09,870 --> 00:13:12,160
Did you pay the gas bill?

140
00:13:14,370 --> 00:13:16,710
-Hey... -Do you realize what you've done?

141
00:13:16,870 --> 00:13:19,710
I'm sorry. I say we bail.

142
00:13:20,040 --> 00:13:21,630
Okay.

143
00:13:30,220 --> 00:13:33,560
Briefcase ain't here. He must have taken it with him.

144
00:13:34,430 --> 00:13:36,140
well, he's gotta come home sometime.

145
00:13:36,310 --> 00:13:39,650
Maybe we should trash the place, send him a little message.

146
00:13:41,150 --> 00:13:43,320
I don't think he's gonna get that message, Joe.

147
00:13:43,480 --> 00:13:45,860
I mean, the guy's got worms in his living room.

148
00:13:46,030 --> 00:13:47,650
Yeah.

149
00:13:48,110 --> 00:13:50,620
Oh, I got a better idea.

150
00:13:53,700 --> 00:13:55,580
I thought I saw a pussy cat.

151
00:13:55,750 --> 00:13:59,420
Oh, I did. I did. Come here.

152
00:14:14,770 --> 00:14:18,940
I can't believe we drove around all day and there's not a single job in this town.

153
00:14:19,100 --> 00:14:21,020
There is nothing, nada, zip.

154
00:14:21,190 --> 00:14:24,020
Yeah, unless you wanna work 40 hours a week.

155
00:14:24,190 --> 00:14:26,400
-Pbbt.  -Here.

156
00:14:26,570 --> 00:14:28,070
I'm gonna go to the store.

157
00:14:28,240 --> 00:14:31,320
Okay, just get the bare essentials. That's the last of our dough.

158
00:14:31,490 --> 00:14:33,870
Hey, what do I look like?

159
00:15:10,780 --> 00:15:12,660
Cripes.

160
00:15:21,330 --> 00:15:23,750
Excuse me, little old lady.

161
00:15:29,420 --> 00:15:33,640
-Do you have change of a dollar? -Change? No, I'm sorry, I don't.

162
00:15:35,050 --> 00:15:38,810
well, could you do me a favor and watch my stuff here...

163
00:15:38,970 --> 00:15:40,350
while I go break a dollar?

164
00:15:40,520 --> 00:15:43,480
-Of course. -Thanks.

165
00:15:44,940 --> 00:15:46,110
I guess they're right.

166
00:15:46,270 --> 00:15:49,940
Senior citizens, although slow and dangerous behind the wheel...

167
00:15:50,110 --> 00:15:52,570
can still serve a purpose.

168
00:15:53,030 --> 00:15:56,530
I'll be right back. Don't you go dying on me.

169
00:16:03,290 --> 00:16:04,540
where's the booze?

170
00:16:05,330 --> 00:16:09,630
I got robbed by a sweet old lady on a motorized cart.

171
00:16:09,800 --> 00:16:12,170
I didn't even see it coming.

172
00:16:14,180 --> 00:16:17,510
-Harry. -No.

173
00:16:17,680 --> 00:16:19,060
Come on, Harry.

174
00:16:19,220 --> 00:16:22,230
-Cheer up. -It gets worse, Lloyd.

175
00:16:22,390 --> 00:16:24,690
My parakeet, Petey?

176
00:16:24,850 --> 00:16:26,060
Yeah?

177
00:16:26,230 --> 00:16:27,940
He's dead.

178
00:16:31,990 --> 00:16:34,070
Oh, man. I'm sorry, Harry.

179
00:16:34,240 --> 00:16:36,200
what happened?

180
00:16:36,780 --> 00:16:38,910
His head fell off.

181
00:16:39,080 --> 00:16:40,990
His head fell off?

182
00:16:41,160 --> 00:16:43,450
Yeah, he was pretty old.

183
00:16:47,920 --> 00:16:49,420
That's it.

184
00:16:49,590 --> 00:16:51,960
I've had it with this dump!

185
00:16:52,130 --> 00:16:55,170
we got no food, we got no jobs...

186
00:16:55,340 --> 00:16:57,180
our pets, heads are falling off!

187
00:16:57,340 --> 00:17:01,760
-Okay, just calm down. -what the hell are we doing here, Harry?

188
00:17:01,930 --> 00:17:03,600
we gotta get out of this town.

189
00:17:03,770 --> 00:17:06,270
Yeah, and go where? where are we gonna go?

190
00:17:06,850 --> 00:17:08,770
I'll tell you where.

191
00:17:09,110 --> 00:17:11,020
Someplace warm.

192
00:17:11,190 --> 00:17:13,990
A place where the beer flows like wine.

193
00:17:14,150 --> 00:17:17,780
where beautiful women instinctively flock like the salmon of Capistrano.

194
00:17:19,950 --> 00:17:24,040
I'm talking about a little place called Aspen.

195
00:17:25,210 --> 00:17:27,620
I don't know, Lloyd. The French are assholes.

196
00:17:28,710 --> 00:17:30,460
wait a minute.

197
00:17:32,130 --> 00:17:34,630
wait a minute. I know what you're up to, mister.

198
00:17:35,300 --> 00:17:39,970
Yeah, you just wanna go to Aspen and find that girl who lost her briefcase...

199
00:17:40,140 --> 00:17:43,260
and you need me to drive you there, right?

200
00:17:43,430 --> 00:17:47,810
-Am I right? Am I right? Am I right, Lloyd? -Yeah. So? Yeah. So?

201
00:17:47,980 --> 00:17:50,270
So I wanna go someplace where we know somebody...

202
00:17:50,440 --> 00:17:52,440
who can plug us into the social pipeline.

203
00:17:52,610 --> 00:17:54,980
No. No, no, no, Lloyd.

204
00:17:55,150 --> 00:17:58,860
No. I say we stay here, we hunt for jobs and we keep saving our money...

205
00:17:59,030 --> 00:18:01,370
for the worm store.

206
00:18:01,530 --> 00:18:04,200
I don't know about you, but I am getting sick and tired...

207
00:18:04,370 --> 00:18:05,830
of running from creditors.

208
00:18:07,160 --> 00:18:09,830
You know what I'm sick and tired of, Harry?

209
00:18:11,590 --> 00:18:14,670
I'm sick and tired of having to eke my way through life.

210
00:18:19,260 --> 00:18:21,180
I'm sick and tired of being a nobody.

211
00:18:23,010 --> 00:18:24,930
But most of all...

212
00:18:29,560 --> 00:18:32,520
I'm sick and tired of having nobody.

213
00:18:35,650 --> 00:18:37,570
Okay, Lloyd.

214
00:18:41,030 --> 00:18:42,320
Aspen it is.

215
00:18:46,200 --> 00:18:48,700
You'd better not be fooling.

216
00:18:54,880 --> 00:18:57,090
Okay, okay.

217
00:18:57,340 --> 00:19:00,630
Just let it out. Have a good cry. Come on.

218
00:19:01,680 --> 00:19:03,050
Okay.

219
00:19:05,560 --> 00:19:07,640
Okay, that's enough.

220
00:19:45,890 --> 00:19:47,560
Lloyd, what are you doing?

221
00:19:47,720 --> 00:19:50,470
It feels like you're running at an incredible rate, Harry.

222
00:19:50,640 --> 00:19:52,600
Quit it. we're not through Connecticut...

223
00:19:52,770 --> 00:19:55,520
-and already you're annoying me. -I'm sorry.

224
00:19:55,940 --> 00:19:58,440
we're really doing it, though, aren't we, buddy?

225
00:20:00,190 --> 00:20:01,940
Hey, where did you get those?

226
00:20:02,110 --> 00:20:04,280
I bought them when we filled up.

227
00:20:04,950 --> 00:20:08,700
But wait, but you...we're supposed to talk about all expenditures, Lloyd.

228
00:20:08,870 --> 00:20:11,160
we are on a very tight budget.

229
00:20:11,330 --> 00:20:13,460
This didn't come out of our travel fund.

230
00:20:13,620 --> 00:20:17,790
No, I was able to raise 25 extra bucks before we left.

231
00:20:18,670 --> 00:20:20,630
where did you get 25 extra bucks?

232
00:20:21,510 --> 00:20:24,220
I sold some stuff to Billy in 4C.

233
00:20:25,340 --> 00:20:29,010
-The blind kid? -Yeah.

234
00:20:29,510 --> 00:20:30,560
Yeah.

235
00:20:31,180 --> 00:20:32,810
what did you sell him, Lloyd?

236
00:20:34,690 --> 00:20:35,980
Stuff.

237
00:20:36,150 --> 00:20:38,150
what kind of stuff?

238
00:20:38,650 --> 00:20:39,860
I don't know.

239
00:20:40,030 --> 00:20:43,240
A few baseball cards, a sack of marbles...

240
00:20:43,400 --> 00:20:44,650
Petey.

241
00:20:45,820 --> 00:20:47,320
Petey?

242
00:20:47,490 --> 00:20:50,660
You sold my dead bird to a blind kid?

243
00:20:51,160 --> 00:20:54,160
Lloyd, the...That...You...what are you...?

244
00:20:54,500 --> 00:20:56,330
Petey didn't even have a head.

245
00:20:56,500 --> 00:20:57,750
Harry...

246
00:20:57,920 --> 00:21:00,040
I took care of it.

247
00:21:02,710 --> 00:21:04,130
Pretty bird.

248
00:21:04,300 --> 00:21:06,180
Yeah, can you say "pretty bird"?

249
00:21:06,340 --> 00:21:07,970
Pretty bird.

250
00:21:08,140 --> 00:21:10,890
Yes, pretty bird.

251
00:21:11,060 --> 00:21:12,970
Pretty bird.

252
00:21:16,520 --> 00:21:17,850
Polly want a cracker?

253
00:21:18,700 --> 00:21:22,020


254
00:21:22,030 --> 00:21:25,440
Those rat bastards. They're rubbing it right in our faces.

255
00:21:25,610 --> 00:21:29,320
Man, Andre'll have a goddamn hemorrhage if we don't get that briefcase back.

256
00:21:29,490 --> 00:21:31,530
They must have been following us for weeks.

257
00:21:31,700 --> 00:21:33,160
why you say?

258
00:21:33,830 --> 00:21:35,040
"Gas Man."

259
00:21:35,210 --> 00:21:38,080
How the hell do they know that I got gas?

260
00:21:38,250 --> 00:21:40,380
They gotta be pros.

261
00:21:41,130 --> 00:21:42,340
Don't worry.

262
00:21:42,500 --> 00:21:44,460
we're gonna get that money back.

263
00:21:45,170 --> 00:21:47,550
And I'll tell you something else.

264
00:21:47,840 --> 00:21:49,720
They ain't never getting to Aspen.

265
00:21:49,890 --> 00:21:51,760
I'm gonna see to that.

266
00:21:57,940 --> 00:22:01,270
They got the Monkees. They were a major influence on the Beatles.

267
00:22:01,440 --> 00:22:03,020
Yeah, I know.

268
00:22:05,190 --> 00:22:07,400
Excuse me, Flo?

269
00:22:15,790 --> 00:22:18,370
Flo, like the TV show.

270
00:22:21,380 --> 00:22:22,710
what is the soup du jour?

271
00:22:22,880 --> 00:22:24,340
It's the soup of the day.

272
00:22:24,960 --> 00:22:28,090
Mm. That sounds good. I'll have that.

273
00:22:29,680 --> 00:22:31,840
Anything else before I leave the area?

274
00:22:32,550 --> 00:22:34,100
No. Yep, yes.

275
00:22:34,260 --> 00:22:37,560
Yes, my soda's flat. It doesn't have any bubbles.

276
00:22:45,110 --> 00:22:46,530
Happy now?

277
00:22:51,570 --> 00:22:55,080
Feels good to mingle with these laid-back country folk, don't it, Har?

278
00:22:55,790 --> 00:22:58,370
I like it a lot.

279
00:23:01,330 --> 00:23:02,960
what? what's the matter?

280
00:23:05,670 --> 00:23:08,460
You spilled the salt. That's what's the matter.

281
00:23:09,300 --> 00:23:12,180
Spilling the salt is very bad luck.

282
00:23:12,340 --> 00:23:15,930
we're driving across the country. The last thing we need is bad luck.

283
00:23:16,100 --> 00:23:19,230
Quick, toss some salt over your right shoulder.

284
00:23:23,360 --> 00:23:24,730
what the hell?

285
00:23:26,690 --> 00:23:28,610
Too little too late, Harry.

286
00:23:31,110 --> 00:23:34,450
who's the dead man that hit me with the salt shaker?

287
00:23:45,340 --> 00:23:48,500
well, oh, that...It was a terrible mistake, sir.

288
00:23:48,670 --> 00:23:52,170
Please, believe me. I would never do anything to offend a man of your size.

289
00:23:52,680 --> 00:23:54,260
Kick his ass, Sea Bass.

290
00:23:56,680 --> 00:23:59,100
-Go ahead, Sea Bass. -You gonna eat that?

291
00:23:59,520 --> 00:24:01,520
what, that? No. Yes. No.

292
00:24:01,690 --> 00:24:05,020
well, no. It crossed my mind. Yeah.

293
00:24:19,620 --> 00:24:20,790
Still want it?

294
00:24:21,870 --> 00:24:23,870
No, you go ahead.

295
00:24:29,670 --> 00:24:32,300
You really wimped out, man.

296
00:24:32,470 --> 00:24:34,380
what are you talking about, "wimped out"?

297
00:24:34,550 --> 00:24:36,220
what, what, did you s...?

298
00:24:36,390 --> 00:24:39,350
-The guy hocked on my burger. what...? -No, no, wait a second.

299
00:24:39,890 --> 00:24:41,640
I think I just...

300
00:24:43,390 --> 00:24:44,560
I just had an idea.

301
00:24:49,320 --> 00:24:51,070
Follow me.

302
00:24:58,490 --> 00:25:00,120
Excuse me, guys.

303
00:25:00,290 --> 00:25:01,870
what the hell do you want?

304
00:25:03,410 --> 00:25:08,830
I just want to apologize for that unpleasant scene a little earlier.

305
00:25:09,290 --> 00:25:12,550
My friend Harry and I would...

306
00:25:12,710 --> 00:25:14,800
like to buy you guys...

307
00:25:14,970 --> 00:25:16,680
a round of beers...

308
00:25:16,840 --> 00:25:18,550
just to bury the hatchet.

309
00:25:19,390 --> 00:25:20,930
Make it four boilermakers.

310
00:25:21,390 --> 00:25:22,770
whatever you want, sir.

311
00:25:22,930 --> 00:25:25,640
I'll have the waitress bring it over immediately.

312
00:25:28,270 --> 00:25:29,770
-Lloyd, what are you doing? -Shh.

313
00:25:29,940 --> 00:25:32,270
-we can't afford to buy them drinks. -Shh.

314
00:25:35,490 --> 00:25:36,950
Excuse me.

315
00:25:38,070 --> 00:25:41,120
Sea Bass and the fellas offered to pick up our check.

316
00:25:41,280 --> 00:25:44,040
They said just put it on their tab.

317
00:25:44,750 --> 00:25:46,870
They're very nice.

318
00:25:48,000 --> 00:25:49,290
Sea Bass said that?

319
00:25:49,880 --> 00:25:54,300
well, if that guy at the table over there is Sea Bass....

320
00:26:02,470 --> 00:26:04,640
All right, if that's what he wants.

321
00:26:06,480 --> 00:26:09,600
-Put these on there too, okay? -You got it.

322
00:26:15,150 --> 00:26:18,490
-Son of a...! -I'm gonna kill those sons of bitches!

323
00:26:23,410 --> 00:26:26,120
That was genius, Lloyd. Sheer genius.

324
00:26:26,290 --> 00:26:28,500
where did you come up with a scam like that?

325
00:26:28,670 --> 00:26:30,250
Saw it in a movie once .

326
00:26:30,420 --> 00:26:32,750
That was incredible.

327
00:26:33,090 --> 00:26:34,960
what happened? Guy tricks some sucker...

328
00:26:35,130 --> 00:26:37,460
into picking up his tab and gets away scot-free?

329
00:26:37,630 --> 00:26:39,130
No. In the movie...

330
00:26:39,300 --> 00:26:43,050
they catch up to him half mile down the road and slit his throat.

331
00:26:43,220 --> 00:26:44,470
It was a good one.

332
00:26:49,810 --> 00:26:52,020
-Harry? -what?

333
00:26:52,190 --> 00:26:55,690
I know this isn't the best time, but when you get a chance to pull over...

334
00:26:55,860 --> 00:26:57,280
-Yeah? -I gotta pee.

335
00:26:57,440 --> 00:26:59,820
what, are you crazy? I'm not pulling over now.

336
00:27:00,280 --> 00:27:03,160
-But I gotta go. what am I supposed to do? -well....

337
00:27:03,330 --> 00:27:07,950
whiz in one of the empty beer bottles. They're on the floor, just get one of...

338
00:27:08,620 --> 00:27:10,210
Quit playing around.

339
00:27:10,710 --> 00:27:12,250
what...? what...?

340
00:27:12,790 --> 00:27:14,500
Shit.

341
00:27:16,880 --> 00:27:18,380
-watch the seat. -Okay.

342
00:27:18,550 --> 00:27:20,590
-watch the seat. -All right.

343
00:27:32,100 --> 00:27:33,190
what? what's wrong?

344
00:27:34,190 --> 00:27:36,320
The bottle's almost full and I'm still going.

345
00:27:36,690 --> 00:27:37,980
-So stop going. -I'm still...

346
00:27:38,150 --> 00:27:41,200
I can't stop going once I've started. It stings.

347
00:27:41,360 --> 00:27:43,070
-Quick, get me another bottle. -what?

348
00:27:43,240 --> 00:27:46,910
Come on, hurry, hurry, hurry. Come on, come on.

349
00:27:47,080 --> 00:27:48,910
-Here, here, here. Go. -Okay.

350
00:27:53,380 --> 00:27:54,580
Hold that.

351
00:28:01,930 --> 00:28:03,590
Hold that one.

352
00:28:04,470 --> 00:28:05,760
Hurry, I'm pitching it.

353
00:28:06,720 --> 00:28:08,260
what are you, a camel?

354
00:28:14,060 --> 00:28:15,270
Pull over.

355
00:28:18,440 --> 00:28:21,490
-Huh? -Pull over.

356
00:28:22,450 --> 00:28:24,780
No, it's a cardigan, but thanks for noticing.

357
00:28:24,950 --> 00:28:26,370
Yeah.

358
00:28:26,530 --> 00:28:27,950
Killer boots, man.

359
00:28:28,950 --> 00:28:32,200
Pull your vehicle to the side of the road.

360
00:28:40,460 --> 00:28:43,340
License and registration, please.

361
00:28:47,050 --> 00:28:50,100
You fellas were going a little fast back there, wouldn't you say?

362
00:28:52,020 --> 00:28:53,310
You....

363
00:28:53,480 --> 00:28:55,850
You fellas been doing a bit of boozing, have you?

364
00:28:56,020 --> 00:28:58,560
Sucking back on grandpa's old cough medicine?

365
00:28:58,730 --> 00:29:01,320
-No. Oh, no, sir. No. -No, no, no.

366
00:29:01,780 --> 00:29:03,990
Yeah, well, what's that?

367
00:29:05,990 --> 00:29:08,410
-That's nothing, sir. -Yeah, nothing.

368
00:29:08,580 --> 00:29:11,660
well, are you aware that it's against the law...

369
00:29:11,830 --> 00:29:15,160
to have an open alcohol container here in the state of Pennsylvania?

370
00:29:15,330 --> 00:29:18,670
Come on. Give me that booze, you little pumpkin-pie-haircutted freak.

371
00:29:18,840 --> 00:29:20,170
Come on.

372
00:29:29,010 --> 00:29:31,310
-Sir, no, I... -No, sir. Don't. Don't drink...

373
00:29:31,470 --> 00:29:35,680
You'd keep your mouth shut if you knew what was good for you, buddy.

374
00:29:52,160 --> 00:29:53,580
Tic Tac, sir?

375
00:29:53,750 --> 00:29:55,120
Get the hell out of here.

376
00:30:01,670 --> 00:30:03,880
How could they not have gotten the ransom?

377
00:30:04,050 --> 00:30:05,760
It just doesn't make sense.

378
00:30:05,920 --> 00:30:08,720
I left the money exactly where they instructed me to.

379
00:30:08,890 --> 00:30:10,720
Oh, it makes perfect sense, Mary.

380
00:30:10,890 --> 00:30:14,430
we should have called the authorities the minute we knew Bobby was kidnapped.

381
00:30:14,600 --> 00:30:18,770
-Helen, we've been through this already. -Mr.Andre.

382
00:30:19,150 --> 00:30:20,690
-Nicholas. -Karl.

383
00:30:20,860 --> 00:30:23,070
-Nick, Nick, Nick. -Nick.

384
00:30:23,230 --> 00:30:24,480
Any word yet, sir?

385
00:30:24,650 --> 00:30:27,240
No. Nothing yet, Nicholas.

386
00:30:28,820 --> 00:30:31,070
I've been giving this a lot of thought.

387
00:30:32,280 --> 00:30:36,040
Maybe we should cancel the preservation benefit.It'll be so easy to re-schedule.

388
00:30:36,200 --> 00:30:38,750
I don't think we should do anything out of the ordinary.

389
00:30:38,920 --> 00:30:40,960
It's imperative that we carry on as usual.

390
00:30:41,130 --> 00:30:43,670
-Okay. -Especially you, Mary.

391
00:30:43,840 --> 00:30:46,920
what am I supposed to do? Go about my life like everything is fine?

392
00:30:47,090 --> 00:30:50,130
-That's exactly what you should do. -Yes. Go skiing. Go to parties.

393
00:30:50,300 --> 00:30:52,430
-Act normally, you know. -Yeah, don't you see?

394
00:30:52,600 --> 00:30:54,350
we can't let on that anything's wrong.

395
00:30:54,510 --> 00:30:58,770
If the press or the authorities get wind of this, the kidnappers may panic.

396
00:31:01,100 --> 00:31:04,020
I mean, you never know what they might do to him then.

397
00:32:00,200 --> 00:32:03,330
So he said, "Do you love me?" And she says, "No...

398
00:32:03,500 --> 00:32:06,130
but that's a real nice ski mask."

399
00:32:12,590 --> 00:32:14,090
Hey, man. what's that?

400
00:35:33,250 --> 00:35:35,170
You want me to drive?

401
00:35:36,170 --> 00:35:38,050
No, I'm cool.

402
00:36:09,910 --> 00:36:11,370
Yes.

403
00:36:11,870 --> 00:36:13,750
-Yeah. -You gonna get it.

404
00:36:13,920 --> 00:36:15,710
Get her.

405
00:36:16,880 --> 00:36:18,670
Oh, yeah, bitch.

406
00:36:23,970 --> 00:36:26,010
This is the life.

407
00:36:26,180 --> 00:36:30,100
Cold beer, a hot tub and paper-thin walls.

408
00:36:32,100 --> 00:36:34,940
There's only one thing that could make this moment any better.

409
00:36:35,100 --> 00:36:36,610
what's that?

410
00:36:36,770 --> 00:36:38,610
If you had a nice set of knockers.

411
00:36:39,860 --> 00:36:41,360
That's two things, Lloyd.

412
00:36:41,530 --> 00:36:44,200
Yeah, well, it's a good thing you're not stacked, Harry...

413
00:36:44,360 --> 00:36:46,820
or I'll be banging you right now.

414
00:36:47,950 --> 00:36:50,490
I'd show you what a real man can do.

415
00:36:50,660 --> 00:36:53,870
Split you like an old piece of firewood.

416
00:36:57,130 --> 00:36:59,590
You'd probably like it too, you big homo.

417
00:36:59,750 --> 00:37:01,300
Shut up.

418
00:37:01,460 --> 00:37:04,260
Don't tell me to shut up, woman.

419
00:37:12,350 --> 00:37:13,980
Yes.

420
00:37:14,140 --> 00:37:16,940
I don't know, Lloyd, this place doesn't really do it for me .

421
00:37:17,100 --> 00:37:19,810
It brings back a lot of memories.

422
00:37:20,980 --> 00:37:22,400


423
00:37:22,900 --> 00:37:24,950
It was a few years ago.

424
00:37:25,740 --> 00:37:27,070
what happened, Harry?

425
00:37:27,240 --> 00:37:30,240
-Some little filly break your heart? -No, it was a girl.

426
00:37:30,410 --> 00:37:32,330
Fraida Felcher.

427
00:37:32,500 --> 00:37:36,790
we stayed in a place just like this. wasn't this classy, but you know, nice.

428
00:37:37,460 --> 00:37:38,670
Felcher?

429
00:37:38,830 --> 00:37:40,210
From Cranston?

430
00:37:40,380 --> 00:37:41,540
Yeah, you know her?

431
00:37:41,710 --> 00:37:44,420
Oh, yeah.

432
00:37:44,590 --> 00:37:46,590
I mean, I remember you...

433
00:37:46,760 --> 00:37:47,970
talking about her.

434
00:37:49,180 --> 00:37:52,180
we had the most incredibly romantic time.

435
00:37:52,350 --> 00:37:55,100
I thought we were gonna be together forever, and then...

436
00:37:55,270 --> 00:37:58,520
About a week later, out of the blue she sends me a John Deere letter.

437
00:37:59,690 --> 00:38:02,230
-She give you any reason? -Yeah, I called her up.

438
00:38:02,400 --> 00:38:05,610
She gave me crap about me not listening to her enough or something.

439
00:38:05,780 --> 00:38:09,860
I don't know, I wasn't paying attention. But the thing that hurt the most...

440
00:38:10,030 --> 00:38:12,200
is I think she was seeing another guy.

441
00:38:15,960 --> 00:38:18,250
Never did find out who.

442
00:38:41,230 --> 00:38:46,030
Mr.Andre, guess who we just happened upon. Yeah. Yeah.

443
00:38:46,190 --> 00:38:49,490
I had plans. I had things I wanted to do.

444
00:38:49,660 --> 00:38:51,490
This is where it ends, in a phone booth.

445
00:38:51,660 --> 00:38:55,740
Yeah, the boys are holed up in a little love nest for the night.

446
00:38:55,910 --> 00:38:58,080
I think they're a little bit strange.

447
00:38:58,500 --> 00:39:01,000
what the hell are these guys up to? I mean...

448
00:39:01,170 --> 00:39:03,080
is it possible they could be feds?

449
00:39:03,250 --> 00:39:06,380
Highly unlikely from what I've seen.

450
00:39:07,550 --> 00:39:12,090
Sir, did you ever hear of the concept of other people?

451
00:39:12,890 --> 00:39:16,770
Me, being that, for the phone, sir...

452
00:39:17,770 --> 00:39:19,640
You turned your back on me. Ooh, ooh!

453
00:39:19,810 --> 00:39:21,350
He got me mad.I almost like it.

454
00:39:21,520 --> 00:39:24,310
You were supposed to grab that bag so we could end this shit.

455
00:39:24,480 --> 00:39:25,610
Here's your drink, baby.

456
00:39:26,110 --> 00:39:29,240
-what I would... -The damage I can do to you.

457
00:39:29,400 --> 00:39:32,530
-Hold on a minute. -Because you were spiteful. I didn't wanna...

458
00:39:34,950 --> 00:39:38,910
That's not your problem. You didn't know.

459
00:39:39,410 --> 00:39:41,120
Get off the phone.

460
00:39:43,790 --> 00:39:45,290
Get off the pho...

461
00:39:50,260 --> 00:39:52,130
I'm sorry, Mr.Andre, you were saying?

462
00:39:52,840 --> 00:39:56,970
Look, Mental, these jokers have got a lot of money and it belongs to me.

463
00:39:57,140 --> 00:39:59,640
I wanna know who they are. what they're doing with it.

464
00:40:01,190 --> 00:40:04,100
I told you already I'm on it. All right?

465
00:40:05,650 --> 00:40:07,110
Good.

466
00:40:11,900 --> 00:40:14,530
According to the map, we've only gone about four inches.

467
00:40:14,700 --> 00:40:16,990
You know, I don't think we have enough gas money.

468
00:40:17,160 --> 00:40:19,490
Relax. we have more than enough.

469
00:40:20,160 --> 00:40:21,500
I think you're wrong, Lloyd.

470
00:40:21,660 --> 00:40:23,580
How much you wanna bet?

471
00:40:23,750 --> 00:40:25,170
I don't bet.

472
00:40:25,330 --> 00:40:27,500
-what do you mean you don't bet? -I don't bet.

473
00:40:27,670 --> 00:40:29,210
-I don't gamble. -Pussy, pussy.

474
00:40:29,380 --> 00:40:31,550
-I never have and I never will. -Pussy.

475
00:40:31,720 --> 00:40:33,680
Yeah, right.

476
00:40:33,840 --> 00:40:36,510
I bet I can get you gambling before the end of the day.

477
00:40:36,680 --> 00:40:37,720
No way.

478
00:40:37,890 --> 00:40:39,350
-I'll give you 3-to-1 odds. -No.

479
00:40:39,520 --> 00:40:40,720
-5-to-1 . -No.

480
00:40:40,890 --> 00:40:42,350
10-to-1?

481
00:40:42,560 --> 00:40:44,060
You're on.

482
00:40:47,270 --> 00:40:49,020
-I'm gonna get you. -Uh-uh.

483
00:40:50,730 --> 00:40:52,860
I don't know how, but I'm gonna get you.

484
00:40:56,870 --> 00:40:59,910
Come on, Joe. Let me do them. Let me do both of them.

485
00:41:00,080 --> 00:41:03,370
-You don't have to worry about it. -Just shut up.

486
00:41:03,540 --> 00:41:05,710
Now, we don't even know who the hell they are.

487
00:41:05,880 --> 00:41:08,630
You don't kill people you don't know. That's a rule.

488
00:41:08,790 --> 00:41:11,500
I want you to get up here, lie down on the front seat.

489
00:41:11,670 --> 00:41:13,050
when they pick me up...

490
00:41:13,220 --> 00:41:15,380
you follow us. You got that?

491
00:41:15,550 --> 00:41:18,510
Keep your shirt on. I gotta squeeze a lemon.

492
00:41:25,900 --> 00:41:27,400
Hey, hey, hey. Here they come.

493
00:41:27,900 --> 00:41:29,810
Stay down. Stay down.

494
00:41:40,990 --> 00:41:43,500
Say, are you guys going to Davenport?

495
00:41:43,950 --> 00:41:47,330
My car died and I'm late for a luncheon.

496
00:41:48,920 --> 00:41:51,920
we usually don't pick up hitchhikers...

497
00:41:52,630 --> 00:41:56,260
but I'm gonna go with my instinct on this one.

498
00:41:56,430 --> 00:41:58,430
Saddle up, partner.

499
00:42:00,600 --> 00:42:02,180
You're it.

500
00:42:02,350 --> 00:42:03,850
-You're it. -You're it, quitsies.

501
00:42:04,020 --> 00:42:06,430
You're it. Quitsies. No anti-quitsies. No startsies.

502
00:42:06,600 --> 00:42:07,850
-You can't do that. -Can to.

503
00:42:08,020 --> 00:42:10,770
-Can't. Stamped it. -Can too. Double stamped it. No erasies.

504
00:42:10,940 --> 00:42:13,940
Cannot. Triple stamped it. No erasies. Touch blue, make it true.

505
00:42:14,110 --> 00:42:16,650
You can't triple stamp a double stamp, Lloyd.

506
00:42:16,820 --> 00:42:19,660
You can't triple stamp a double stamp. You...Lloyd.Lloyd.

507
00:42:19,820 --> 00:42:22,740
Guys! Enough!

508
00:42:28,000 --> 00:42:30,920
wanna hear the most annoying sound in the world?

509
00:42:33,920 --> 00:42:37,300
Guys! Guys! Guys!

510
00:42:38,680 --> 00:42:40,390
Fellas...

511
00:42:41,470 --> 00:42:44,560
you think we could listen to the radio or something?

512
00:42:46,270 --> 00:42:47,980
Radio?

513
00:42:48,310 --> 00:42:50,810
who needs a radio? Ready, Harry?

514
00:43:00,490 --> 00:43:05,490
-Mockingbird, everybody have you heard? -Mockingbird, everybody have you heard?

515
00:43:05,660 --> 00:43:09,790
-She's gonna buy me a mockingbird -She's gonna buy me a mockingbird

516
00:43:09,960 --> 00:43:13,460
-And if that mockingbird don't sing -And if that mockingbird don't sing

517
00:43:13,630 --> 00:43:17,760
-She's gonna buy me a diamond ring -She's gonna buy me a diamond ring

518
00:43:17,920 --> 00:43:20,720
-And if that diamond ring don't shine -And if that diamond...

519
00:43:20,880 --> 00:43:22,970
Lloyd, there's people who want a ride too.

520
00:43:23,140 --> 00:43:25,010
Pick them up.

521
00:43:46,040 --> 00:43:48,830
You want an Atomic Pepper, Mr. Mentalino?

522
00:43:50,370 --> 00:43:51,790
No.

523
00:43:51,960 --> 00:43:53,830
You guys go ahead.

524
00:43:54,000 --> 00:43:55,710
I'll do it if you will, Lloyd.

525
00:43:55,880 --> 00:43:57,710
Okay. You go first.

526
00:43:57,880 --> 00:43:59,170
No. Uh-uh. No. You go first.

527
00:43:59,340 --> 00:44:01,880
-No, you go first. No, you go first. -No, you go first.

528
00:44:02,050 --> 00:44:03,800
-You go. I always go first. -Oh, yeah.

529
00:44:03,970 --> 00:44:08,510
why don't you guys both stop acting like a couple of pussies...

530
00:44:08,680 --> 00:44:11,140
and go at the same time, huh?

531
00:44:12,850 --> 00:44:15,730
-That sounds like a dare, Harry. -It's a double dare.

532
00:44:15,900 --> 00:44:18,190
Yeah, okay. You're on.

533
00:44:26,580 --> 00:44:28,580
-It's not so bad. -well?

534
00:44:28,740 --> 00:44:31,500
-It's more tingly than hot. -Yeah.

535
00:44:44,390 --> 00:44:47,930
Now, if you fellas would excuse me, I gotta use the phone.

536
00:44:48,310 --> 00:44:50,720
Enjoy your meal, guys.

537
00:44:52,810 --> 00:44:56,600
Here, Lloyd. This helps. Here.

538
00:44:56,770 --> 00:44:58,860
It works good.

539
00:45:05,280 --> 00:45:07,200
Yeah, it's Mental.

540
00:45:07,620 --> 00:45:10,410
I'm just sitting down to a nice meal with our boys.

541
00:45:10,580 --> 00:45:13,790
How nice for you. Don't forget that your bread plate is on the left.

542
00:45:13,960 --> 00:45:16,710
Look, I can't have these guys running around Aspen.

543
00:45:16,880 --> 00:45:19,790
Don't worry. They ain't gonna be running around nowhere...

544
00:45:19,960 --> 00:45:23,340
after I dump a little rat poison in their Shirley Temple.

545
00:45:27,510 --> 00:45:29,800
Good, good.

546
00:45:30,350 --> 00:45:33,020
-That's good. -Here he comes. Here he comes.

547
00:45:34,690 --> 00:45:39,110
-Feeling better, girls? -Yes, much better. Thank you for asking.

548
00:45:45,570 --> 00:45:47,740
So why you going to Aspen? Vacation?

549
00:45:49,160 --> 00:45:51,330
why don't you eat up and we'll tell you.

550
00:45:52,580 --> 00:45:55,250
It just doesn't seem like you packed much.

551
00:45:55,410 --> 00:45:58,170
All I saw was one bag and a briefcase.

552
00:45:58,920 --> 00:46:02,420
No, no, the briefcase isn't even ours. Some lady left it at the airport.

553
00:46:02,590 --> 00:46:05,670
we're just bringing it back to her. How's your burger?

554
00:46:07,890 --> 00:46:10,510
You mean you don't even know her?

555
00:46:19,230 --> 00:46:24,610
Talk about being in the wrong place at the wrong time.

556
00:46:54,310 --> 00:46:56,640
Are you okay, man? It was just a goof.

557
00:46:57,180 --> 00:46:58,350
My ulcer.

558
00:46:58,520 --> 00:47:01,400
Quick, quick, my pills.

559
00:47:01,560 --> 00:47:03,400
Somebody should call an ambulance.

560
00:47:03,570 --> 00:47:06,780
Look, you get the pills. Don't worry, I know CPR.

561
00:47:06,940 --> 00:47:10,240
-I'll get the pills. -Out with the bad air, in with the good.

562
00:47:10,410 --> 00:47:12,410
Out with the bad air...

563
00:47:20,920 --> 00:47:22,420
No.

564
00:47:25,170 --> 00:47:27,130
This is a lot easier if you just lay back.

565
00:47:27,300 --> 00:47:28,920
Here, here.

566
00:47:29,090 --> 00:47:30,760
-Here. -He's resisting me.

567
00:47:30,930 --> 00:47:33,680
Here. Here you go. Here you go. Here you go.

568
00:47:33,850 --> 00:47:35,680
-Pills. Okay. -Here you go. There you go.

569
00:47:35,850 --> 00:47:39,730
-Pills are good. Pills are good. -Drink them down. Drink them down.

570
00:47:40,270 --> 00:47:43,150
-There you go. There you go, big guy. -That's better.

571
00:47:43,310 --> 00:47:45,610
You want some ketchup and mustard? That helped us.

572
00:47:45,770 --> 00:47:47,440
Yeah.

573
00:47:49,610 --> 00:47:51,450
You son of a...bitch!

574
00:48:03,210 --> 00:48:05,130
Check, please.

575
00:48:08,460 --> 00:48:10,630
I can't believe it.

576
00:48:11,300 --> 00:48:13,630
Life's a fragile thing, Har.

577
00:48:13,800 --> 00:48:17,470
One minute you're chewing on a burger, the next minute you're dead meat.

578
00:48:17,640 --> 00:48:19,560
But he blamed me.

579
00:48:19,730 --> 00:48:21,810
You heard him. Those were his last words.

580
00:48:23,310 --> 00:48:25,400
Not if you count the gurgling sound.

581
00:48:29,940 --> 00:48:31,280
You mean he was poisoned?

582
00:48:31,450 --> 00:48:32,780
No doubt about it.

583
00:48:32,950 --> 00:48:35,530
They found these next to the body.

584
00:48:36,330 --> 00:48:37,830
-Sir. -Yeah?

585
00:48:37,990 --> 00:48:40,830
waitress says he came in with a couple of younger guys.

586
00:48:41,000 --> 00:48:43,830
They called the ambulance and then they hit the road.

587
00:48:44,000 --> 00:48:46,500
-Any idea where they were going? -we received a report.

588
00:48:46,670 --> 00:48:49,590
They were seen headed west on l-80 towards Colorado.

589
00:48:50,130 --> 00:48:52,340
Did you get a make on the vehicle?

590
00:48:53,430 --> 00:48:54,930
Yes, sir.

591
00:48:55,090 --> 00:48:58,180
They're driving an '84 ...

592
00:48:58,600 --> 00:48:59,640
sheepdog.

593
00:49:57,570 --> 00:49:59,410
Skis, huh?

594
00:49:59,910 --> 00:50:02,160
-That's right. -Great.

595
00:50:03,080 --> 00:50:04,910
They yours?

596
00:50:06,120 --> 00:50:07,920
Uh-huh.

597
00:50:10,790 --> 00:50:11,840
Both of them?

598
00:50:14,340 --> 00:50:15,590
Yeah.

599
00:50:17,380 --> 00:50:19,090
Cool.

600
00:50:23,100 --> 00:50:26,600
Excuse me, but you...You're spraying everywhere.

601
00:50:39,160 --> 00:50:42,830


602
00:51:20,160 --> 00:51:22,990
Oh, man, you gotta be shitting me.

603
00:51:23,160 --> 00:51:24,830
If it ain't my old friend.

604
00:51:26,660 --> 00:51:31,080
You're right on time.

605
00:51:40,050 --> 00:51:42,300
That's a lot of luggage for a little vacation.

606
00:51:42,470 --> 00:51:43,930
Oh, I'm moving to Aspen.

607
00:51:44,100 --> 00:51:47,350
I've gotta get away from my boyfriend. He's such a klutz.

608
00:51:47,520 --> 00:51:51,520
Plus my astrologer told me that I really should stay away from accident-prone guys.

609
00:51:51,690 --> 00:51:54,560
well, you know, l...

610
00:51:57,530 --> 00:52:00,530
Here, it's a little loose. You might wanna...

611
00:52:00,990 --> 00:52:02,570
-Thank you. -No, hey, no.Allow me.

612
00:52:02,740 --> 00:52:07,950
I've got a thing of thing...Here, got them right here. Right here.

613
00:52:14,290 --> 00:52:15,630
Thank you.

614
00:52:15,790 --> 00:52:19,000
Sure. You know, I'm heading up to Aspen myself.

615
00:52:19,170 --> 00:52:23,380
Maybe we could, you know, meet up, have some hot chocolate or something.

616
00:52:24,140 --> 00:52:25,180
Sure, why not.

617
00:52:25,350 --> 00:52:26,390
You seem harmless.

618
00:52:27,140 --> 00:52:28,470
I'm gonna give you my number.

619
00:52:28,640 --> 00:52:30,180
-Let me find a pen though. -Great.

620
00:52:30,350 --> 00:52:33,270
Let's see. I know I have one in here somewhere.

621
00:52:33,440 --> 00:52:36,060
Look, just tell it to me. I got a really good memory.

622
00:52:36,230 --> 00:52:38,230
-well, the number's 555... -555.

623
00:52:38,400 --> 00:52:41,400
905...wait a minute, that's my old number.

624
00:52:41,570 --> 00:52:43,740
That is so weird how your mind goes blank...

625
00:52:43,910 --> 00:52:46,570
For God's sakes just give me the damn number!

626
00:52:47,490 --> 00:52:50,580
Okay, look, you're gonna get pushy, forget about it.

627
00:52:56,920 --> 00:52:58,880
Find a happy place.

628
00:52:59,050 --> 00:53:01,880
Find a happy place. Find a happy place.

629
00:53:02,050 --> 00:53:04,430
I'll show you a happy place.

630
00:53:05,550 --> 00:53:07,760
Here's your happy place.

631
00:53:52,350 --> 00:53:55,060
Go around now. Go around.

632
00:53:57,810 --> 00:54:00,940
-All right. Any sign of them? -No, but we're expecting them shortly.

633
00:54:01,110 --> 00:54:03,980
A motorist saw a pooch about 30 miles back headed this way.

634
00:54:09,780 --> 00:54:12,030
Look, I told you what happened, so just drop it.

635
00:54:12,200 --> 00:54:14,450
Yeah, okay. Sure thing, Lloyd. Sure thing.

636
00:54:15,460 --> 00:54:18,420
I promise not to mention another word...

637
00:54:18,580 --> 00:54:22,460
about being in a bathroom with a 6'4" trucker with his pants down.

638
00:54:31,760 --> 00:54:34,180
Hey, look, we're almost in Colorado.

639
00:54:34,520 --> 00:54:38,520
what do you say we change seats? I've been driving for nine straight hours.

640
00:54:38,690 --> 00:54:41,690
I don't have the energy to start a new state.

641
00:54:41,860 --> 00:54:45,820
-why should I do you any favors? -I'll let you kiss me.

642
00:54:46,950 --> 00:54:50,110
I swear I'm gonna...

643
00:54:50,280 --> 00:54:53,200
Take your...I'm gonna...Swear to God I'm gonna take...

644
00:54:53,370 --> 00:54:57,370
Oh, don't...Don't touch me.

645
00:55:03,300 --> 00:55:05,800
I'm done, okay. Enough.

646
00:55:18,100 --> 00:55:22,400
Hey, guys. Oh, Big Gulps, huh? All right.

647
00:55:22,730 --> 00:55:24,770
well, see you later.

648
00:55:28,360 --> 00:55:31,070
Hey, Harry, I got some beef jerk...

649
00:55:35,700 --> 00:55:38,950
Some people just weren't cut out for life on the road.

650
00:55:49,000 --> 00:55:50,950


651
00:56:14,490 --> 00:56:17,530
I was wondering when you were gonna get up.

652
00:56:19,410 --> 00:56:22,290
well, how long have I been out?

653
00:56:23,380 --> 00:56:26,630
I'd say a good five hours.

654
00:56:30,760 --> 00:56:36,640
Huh. I expected the Rocky Mountains to be a little rockier than this.

655
00:56:37,600 --> 00:56:39,970
I was thinking the same thing.

656
00:56:40,310 --> 00:56:43,690
That John Denver is full of shit, man.

657
00:56:47,570 --> 00:56:49,320
I'm only human, Harry.

658
00:56:50,150 --> 00:56:52,650
Anybody can make a mistake.

659
00:56:53,200 --> 00:56:54,530
Come on.

660
00:56:54,700 --> 00:56:56,530
Stop being a baby.

661
00:56:56,700 --> 00:56:58,660
So we backtracked a tad.

662
00:56:58,830 --> 00:57:00,580
A tad?

663
00:57:01,330 --> 00:57:02,960
A tad, Lloyd?

664
00:57:03,120 --> 00:57:10,000
You drove almost a sixth of the way across the country in the wrong direction!

665
00:57:11,010 --> 00:57:13,170
Now we don't have enough money to get to Aspen.

666
00:57:13,340 --> 00:57:16,760
we don't have enough money to get home! we don't have enough money to eat!

667
00:57:16,930 --> 00:57:20,060
we don't have enough money to sleep!

668
00:57:22,680 --> 00:57:26,020
well, it's not gonna do us any good to sit here whining about it.

669
00:57:26,190 --> 00:57:27,900
we're in a hole.

670
00:57:28,060 --> 00:57:31,190
we're just gonna have to dig ourselves out.

671
00:57:32,820 --> 00:57:34,070
Okay. Right. You're right.

672
00:57:34,240 --> 00:57:35,860
You're absolutely right, Lloyd.

673
00:57:36,030 --> 00:57:37,870
where you going?

674
00:57:38,370 --> 00:57:41,660
Home. I'm walking home.

675
00:57:42,120 --> 00:57:46,580
Oh, well, pardon me, Mr.Perfect!

676
00:57:46,830 --> 00:57:50,710
I guess I forgot that you never, ever make a mistake.

677
00:58:14,990 --> 00:58:19,160
Harry!

678
00:58:21,830 --> 00:58:23,700
Harry. wait up.

679
00:58:38,760 --> 00:58:41,430
Got room for one more if you still wanna go to Aspen.

680
00:58:42,260 --> 00:58:43,680
where did you find that?

681
00:58:44,930 --> 00:58:47,060
Some kid back in town.

682
00:58:47,230 --> 00:58:49,480
Traded the van for it, straight up.

683
00:58:49,650 --> 00:58:52,900
I can get 70 miles to the gallon on this hog.

684
00:58:57,570 --> 00:58:59,110
You know, Lloyd...

685
00:58:59,280 --> 00:59:03,530
just when I think you couldn't possibly be any dumber...

686
00:59:04,870 --> 00:59:07,790
you go and do something like this...

687
00:59:09,120 --> 00:59:11,710
and totally redeem yourself!

688
00:59:15,050 --> 00:59:17,340
-Still wanna go to Aspen? -Oh, yeah.

689
00:59:17,510 --> 00:59:20,470
-Okay. Let's go, buddy. -Super!

690
00:59:24,470 --> 00:59:27,600
-Lloyd, no, west.Go west, Lloyd. -Oh, yeah.

691
01:00:13,520 --> 01:00:17,360
I got...I gotta stop and go to the bathroom.

692
01:00:18,360 --> 01:00:20,280
Just go, man.

693
01:00:25,370 --> 01:00:27,160
That sure is warm.

694
01:01:28,640 --> 01:01:30,760
we're there.

695
01:01:39,940 --> 01:01:43,570
Got a little nippy going through the pass, huh, Har?

696
01:01:46,780 --> 01:01:48,450
lsn't this incredible?

697
01:01:48,870 --> 01:01:52,330
-what more could two single guys ask for? -How about some food?

698
01:01:52,500 --> 01:01:55,790
I swallowed a big June bug when we were driving.I'm not really hungry.

699
01:01:55,960 --> 01:01:58,130
Yeah, well, I'm starving.

700
01:01:59,170 --> 01:02:01,040
Jeez, look at the butt on that.

701
01:02:02,000 --> 01:02:03,210
Yeah.

702
01:02:03,800 --> 01:02:05,800
He must work out.

703
01:02:06,470 --> 01:02:09,970
Hey. why don't we get busy and deliver the briefcase to Mary.

704
01:02:10,140 --> 01:02:13,890
If I know her as well as I think I do, she'll invite us in for tea and strumpets.

705
01:02:14,060 --> 01:02:15,980
Good plan.where does she live?

706
01:02:16,140 --> 01:02:17,730
I don't know.

707
01:02:18,980 --> 01:02:21,270
what's her last name? I'll look it up.

708
01:02:23,940 --> 01:02:26,530
You know, I don't really recall.

709
01:02:26,700 --> 01:02:28,110
It starts with an S.

710
01:02:28,280 --> 01:02:31,490
Swim, Swamie, Slippy...

711
01:02:31,660 --> 01:02:34,370
Slappy, Slimin, Solmon, Simmon...

712
01:02:34,540 --> 01:02:37,000
Swan, Swenson, Swanson?

713
01:02:37,170 --> 01:02:40,130
-Maybe it's on the briefcase. Look on... -Yeah. It's right here.

714
01:02:40,290 --> 01:02:42,710
Samsonite. I was way off.

715
01:02:42,880 --> 01:02:44,590
I knew it started with an S, though.

716
01:02:46,170 --> 01:02:48,340
I'm not seeing it here, Lloyd.

717
01:02:48,510 --> 01:02:50,550
She must be unlisted.

718
01:02:53,810 --> 01:02:55,180
Great.

719
01:02:55,350 --> 01:02:57,680
So, what are we supposed to do now?

720
01:03:02,110 --> 01:03:05,150
I can't feeI my fingers anymore , Lloyd.

721
01:03:06,240 --> 01:03:07,860
They're numb.

722
01:03:11,030 --> 01:03:13,700
Maybe you should wear these extra gloves.

723
01:03:13,870 --> 01:03:15,990
My hands are starting to get sweaty.

724
01:03:17,040 --> 01:03:19,250
Extra gloves?

725
01:03:20,040 --> 01:03:24,340
You've had this pair of extra gloves this whole time?

726
01:03:26,090 --> 01:03:29,220
Yeah. we're in the Rockies.

727
01:03:31,220 --> 01:03:32,550
I'm going to kill you.

728
01:03:33,890 --> 01:03:35,430
what?

729
01:03:35,600 --> 01:03:38,930
I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna kill you, Lloyd.

730
01:03:39,100 --> 01:03:41,350
-Calm down. -Right now. I'm gonna kill you.

731
01:03:41,520 --> 01:03:43,560
Harry, you got that crazy look in your eye.

732
01:03:48,150 --> 01:03:50,400
-I know what I'm gonna do. -what are you doing?

733
01:03:50,570 --> 01:03:53,820
I'm gonna do something I should have done a long time ago.

734
01:03:55,580 --> 01:03:57,080
Don't do anything foolish, Harry.

735
01:03:57,250 --> 01:03:59,750
what? Foolish? This isn't foolish.

736
01:03:59,910 --> 01:04:04,000
I'm gonna toss this damn curse right into that damn pond.

737
01:04:06,880 --> 01:04:09,590
-You're an asshole.No! Harry! -I'm gonna do it.

738
01:04:09,920 --> 01:04:11,590
Stop...

739
01:04:14,220 --> 01:04:15,600
Harry...

740
01:04:15,760 --> 01:04:17,930
your hands are freezing.

741
01:04:20,600 --> 01:04:22,690
Harry. Look.

742
01:04:22,850 --> 01:04:25,110
Look. Look.

743
01:04:31,110 --> 01:04:33,570
Okay, here's the plan.

744
01:04:33,740 --> 01:04:36,700
we borrow a few bucks, just a small loan, from the briefcase...

745
01:04:36,870 --> 01:04:39,410
-and we find some reasonable lodgings. -Good plan.

746
01:04:39,580 --> 01:04:41,960
we'll keep track all the money we spend with IOU's.

747
01:04:42,120 --> 01:04:45,420
we'll be meticulous to the last penny. whatever we borrow, we pay back.

748
01:04:45,590 --> 01:04:48,670
-Absolute...we're good for it. -Our word is our bond.

749
01:04:50,920 --> 01:04:54,300
This is the Hotel Danbury presidential suite, gentlemen.

750
01:04:54,470 --> 01:04:58,140
Normally reserved for royalty, visiting dignitaries...

751
01:04:58,310 --> 01:05:00,520
illustrious stars of stage and screen.

752
01:05:00,680 --> 01:05:03,810
we have shortly coming the emperor and empress of Japan.

753
01:05:03,980 --> 01:05:07,060
And of course, Prince Charles and Di when they were together...

754
01:05:07,230 --> 01:05:10,610
-used to frequent the hotel constantly. -we'll take it.

755
01:05:40,430 --> 01:05:42,020
There you go.

756
01:05:44,480 --> 01:05:45,940
-There you go. -Thank you, sir.

757
01:05:46,100 --> 01:05:47,560
-There you go. -Thank you, sir.

758
01:05:47,730 --> 01:05:49,270
-There you go. -Thank you, sir.

759
01:05:49,440 --> 01:05:51,360
There you go.

760
01:05:57,780 --> 01:06:01,700
Rain brought them to him. My mother was Sarah Carver.

761
01:06:01,870 --> 01:06:05,830
Although at the time he wasn't sure he wanted to accept the gift.

762
01:06:06,000 --> 01:06:08,460
Ned, do you think he'll let us stay?

763
01:06:08,630 --> 01:06:13,760
No, this place is ugly anyway. You and me , we're family.

764
01:06:13,920 --> 01:06:15,550
I promise never to take you away.

765
01:06:16,380 --> 01:06:18,720
And no one's ever gonna break us apart.

766
01:06:18,890 --> 01:06:22,350
At pacific Bell, we believe that's pretty special.

767
01:06:22,600 --> 01:06:25,230
Oh, boy. This is living, huh?

768
01:06:25,390 --> 01:06:27,560
-Yeah. -what's on next?

769
01:06:27,730 --> 01:06:30,020
I don't know. Let me look it up.

770
01:06:32,480 --> 01:06:34,360
Lloyd, you okay?

771
01:06:34,530 --> 01:06:35,740
Harry...

772
01:06:35,900 --> 01:06:37,570
it's Mary.

773
01:06:37,740 --> 01:06:40,660
-who? -Mary. with the briefcase?

774
01:06:42,030 --> 01:06:43,910
Mary Swanson.

775
01:06:44,410 --> 01:06:48,920
Swanson. "will host a newl...."

776
01:06:49,080 --> 01:06:50,750
-"Host annual." -"Host...

777
01:06:50,920 --> 01:06:52,210
annual...

778
01:06:52,380 --> 01:06:55,260
-Annual. -annual meeting of...

779
01:07:02,430 --> 01:07:03,760
It's a big one.

780
01:07:03,930 --> 01:07:06,850
"International Preservationists Society tomorrow night."

781
01:07:10,020 --> 01:07:13,900
well, come on, Cinderella, we gotta get you ready for the ball.

782
01:09:06,890 --> 01:09:07,890
Thanks, Barn.

783
01:09:08,060 --> 01:09:10,520
-There you go. -Thank you, sir.

784
01:09:24,740 --> 01:09:26,570
You're right.

785
01:09:27,490 --> 01:09:29,410
Okay, okay, okay.

786
01:09:29,580 --> 01:09:33,080
-Cripes. -Yes, yes, yes.

787
01:09:39,250 --> 01:09:40,420
Time out.

788
01:09:40,590 --> 01:09:42,050
Okay, time out.whatever.

789
01:09:42,210 --> 01:09:46,380
Excuse me, gentlemen. This is a $500-a-plate dinner. Good night.

790
01:09:46,550 --> 01:09:49,260
Oh, 500 . Oh, okay. All right, no problem.

791
01:09:49,430 --> 01:09:52,220
Here, put us down for...Put us down for four.

792
01:09:52,390 --> 01:09:54,560
In case we want seconds.

793
01:10:00,610 --> 01:10:02,230
Jesus Christ.

794
01:10:02,400 --> 01:10:03,530
It's them.

795
01:10:03,690 --> 01:10:07,360
-Them who? -Them. The guys who whacked Mental.

796
01:10:09,240 --> 01:10:10,990
Can't you just feel it, Harry?

797
01:10:11,160 --> 01:10:13,450
This is our big chance, man.

798
01:10:13,620 --> 01:10:16,920
All we gotta do is show a little class, a little sophistication...

799
01:10:17,080 --> 01:10:19,330
-and we're in like a dirty shirt. -No problem.

800
01:10:19,500 --> 01:10:22,630
we can be classy and sophis...Look at the funbags on that hosehound.

801
01:10:22,800 --> 01:10:24,170
I'd like to eat her liver...

802
01:10:24,340 --> 01:10:27,970
with some farver beans and a nice bottle of Chianti.

803
01:10:30,550 --> 01:10:32,640
Come on. Let's go get bowls of loudmouth soup.

804
01:10:32,810 --> 01:10:34,390
Yeah.

805
01:10:35,310 --> 01:10:39,400
-Hey, bartender, two martinis, please. -Yes, sir.Right away.

806
01:10:39,690 --> 01:10:41,770
Ladies and gentlemen, your attention, please.

807
01:10:42,150 --> 01:10:46,110
The Aspen Preservation Society is the world's foremost defender...

808
01:10:46,280 --> 01:10:49,070
of 23 endangered species.

809
01:10:49,240 --> 01:10:54,540
And it is with tremendous honor that we're able to bring Mr.Swanson forward...

810
01:10:54,700 --> 01:10:58,750
to introduce us to the 24th, everybody.Karl.

811
01:10:58,960 --> 01:11:04,340
Thank you.

812
01:11:05,090 --> 01:11:06,670
Ladies and gentlemen...

813
01:11:06,840 --> 01:11:09,760
I give you the lcelandic Snow Owl.

814
01:11:17,690 --> 01:11:19,310
These magnificent specimens...

815
01:11:19,480 --> 01:11:23,860
constitute one-seventh of the snow owl population left on the planet.

816
01:11:24,020 --> 01:11:25,650
And God willing...

817
01:11:25,820 --> 01:11:28,820
with your help and that of the Society's...

818
01:11:28,990 --> 01:11:32,160
these wonderful creatures will flourish once more.

819
01:11:32,320 --> 01:11:35,540
Thank you again and enjoy your evening.

820
01:11:37,870 --> 01:11:40,210
Could I have some pistachios, please?

821
01:11:42,130 --> 01:11:43,630
And another one of those.

822
01:11:43,790 --> 01:11:48,260
Lloyd, what are you doing? would you calm down? I've never seen you so nervous.

823
01:11:49,010 --> 01:11:51,260
Keep an eye on them, Shay.

824
01:11:51,430 --> 01:11:52,640
Keep a close eye.

825
01:11:52,800 --> 01:11:54,720
I'm ready for commitment, Harry.

826
01:11:54,890 --> 01:11:57,720
First time I set eyes on Mary Swanson...

827
01:11:57,890 --> 01:12:01,390
I just got that old-fashioned romantic feeling...

828
01:12:01,560 --> 01:12:04,020
where I'd do anything to bone her.

829
01:12:04,190 --> 01:12:07,730
-That's a special feeling, Lloyd.Yeah. -Oh, yeah?

830
01:12:08,440 --> 01:12:11,030
Oh, my. There she is.

831
01:12:11,200 --> 01:12:13,490
wow, you weren't kidding, Lloyd.

832
01:12:13,660 --> 01:12:14,910
She's an angel.

833
01:12:17,700 --> 01:12:20,580
what are you waiting for? Get over there and talk to her.

834
01:12:25,920 --> 01:12:29,920
She's gonna think I'm a psycho when she finds out how far I came just to see her.

835
01:12:30,090 --> 01:12:31,920
You know what you have. Her briefcase.

836
01:12:32,090 --> 01:12:34,720
She's gonna be thrilled to see you.

837
01:12:36,260 --> 01:12:38,770
wait, I have an idea.

838
01:12:40,020 --> 01:12:44,190
why don't you go over and introduce yourself...

839
01:12:44,360 --> 01:12:48,440
and that way you can build me up so I won't have to brag about myself later.

840
01:12:48,610 --> 01:12:54,530
Tell her I'm rich and I'm good-looking and I have a rapist wit.

841
01:12:54,700 --> 01:12:56,660
No.I don't...No.I don't think I could.

842
01:12:56,830 --> 01:12:59,950
-No, I'm not...That's not... -Come on, please.Oh, Har, please.

843
01:13:00,120 --> 01:13:02,580
-Please. -Okay, okay, okay, stop.

844
01:13:02,750 --> 01:13:04,460
what are you gonna do?

845
01:13:04,630 --> 01:13:06,790
I'm gonna hang by the bar...

846
01:13:07,130 --> 01:13:09,000
put out the vibe.

847
01:13:09,460 --> 01:13:10,960
Okay.

848
01:13:21,350 --> 01:13:23,810
Nice set of hooters you got there.

849
01:13:25,520 --> 01:13:28,650
-I beg your pardon. -The owls. They're beautiful.

850
01:13:32,610 --> 01:13:34,070
Yeah.

851
01:13:34,990 --> 01:13:36,570
Are you a bird lover?

852
01:13:36,740 --> 01:13:39,870
Me? Oh, no. well, I used to have a parakeet...

853
01:13:40,040 --> 01:13:44,250
but now my main area of expertise is canines.

854
01:13:44,420 --> 01:13:47,670
Dogs, to the layperson.

855
01:13:48,290 --> 01:13:49,960
Thanks.

856
01:13:51,210 --> 01:13:53,460
I love dogs too.

857
01:13:53,920 --> 01:13:57,340
-So how are you involved with them? -Oh, I...You know, I've trained them.

858
01:13:57,510 --> 01:14:00,180
You know, bathed them, clipped them. I've even bred them.

859
01:14:00,350 --> 01:14:02,520
Oh, really? Any unusual breeding?

860
01:14:02,680 --> 01:14:04,350
No, mostly just doggie style.

861
01:14:05,850 --> 01:14:10,150
One time, we successfully mated a bulldog with a Shih Tzu.

862
01:14:11,020 --> 01:14:13,860
Really? That's weird.

863
01:14:14,400 --> 01:14:16,360
Yeah, we called it a bullshit.

864
01:14:27,500 --> 01:14:32,340
Oh, I'm...Anyway, the reaI reason I came over here was to...

865
01:14:32,500 --> 01:14:35,210
I gotta introduce you to a buddy of mine .

866
01:14:35,380 --> 01:14:37,880
Oh, Mary, I don't believe I've met your friend.

867
01:14:38,050 --> 01:14:41,220
Oh, well, actually, we haven't been properly introduced.

868
01:14:41,390 --> 01:14:42,850
My name is Mary Swanson.

869
01:14:43,020 --> 01:14:45,390
-Hi, Harry Dunne. -Hi, nice to meet you.

870
01:14:45,560 --> 01:14:46,890
This is my stepmother, Helen.

871
01:14:47,060 --> 01:14:49,730
Hi, Harry Dunne. Pleasure to meet you both.

872
01:14:49,900 --> 01:14:53,480
well, I saw you come in. I was hoping I'd get a chance to meet you.

873
01:14:53,650 --> 01:14:55,690
-You were? Really. -Yes.

874
01:14:55,860 --> 01:14:58,110
That tuxedo, it's fabulous.

875
01:14:58,280 --> 01:15:00,320
Really, I love a man with a sense of humor.

876
01:15:00,490 --> 01:15:03,280
Really. And so does Mary. It's hysterical.

877
01:15:03,450 --> 01:15:05,240
-Really? -Oh, yes.

878
01:15:07,500 --> 01:15:10,580
-Anyway, yeah, about my friend... -what are you doing tomorrow?

879
01:15:10,750 --> 01:15:13,210
Mary is looking for someone to hit the slopes with.

880
01:15:13,380 --> 01:15:15,670
She what? Huh?

881
01:15:15,840 --> 01:15:18,050
Helen, you're embarrassing me.

882
01:15:18,220 --> 01:15:19,510
Yeah, well, you are.

883
01:15:19,680 --> 01:15:22,390
After all, the snow's gonna be gone in a couple of weeks...

884
01:15:22,550 --> 01:15:26,100
and this may be your last chance. She never gets a chance to get out.

885
01:15:26,270 --> 01:15:29,020
well, what do you say, Mr.Dunne? Are you available?

886
01:15:29,600 --> 01:15:32,610
-I don't know. My friend... -Forget about your friend for one day.

887
01:15:32,770 --> 01:15:35,730
I think you kids will have a wonderful time. what do you say?

888
01:15:36,440 --> 01:15:42,490
well, you know, I don't know, you know, the thing, part...Sure, what time?

889
01:15:47,580 --> 01:15:49,870
How come you didn't bring her over?

890
01:15:50,670 --> 01:15:53,960
Relax, you're golden. I got you a date with her tomorrow.

891
01:15:54,130 --> 01:16:00,170
Oh, you are...what? I can't...This...I love you, man.

892
01:16:00,340 --> 01:16:02,470
Okay, okay, you're kissing me.

893
01:16:02,640 --> 01:16:05,010
-You're kissing me, Lloyd... -I love you.

894
01:16:05,180 --> 01:16:07,310
Oh, God.

895
01:16:07,470 --> 01:16:10,640
This calls for a little of the bubbly.

896
01:16:10,810 --> 01:16:12,480
-You're gonna be my best man. -Good.

897
01:16:12,650 --> 01:16:13,690
-I promise. -Thank you.

898
01:16:13,860 --> 01:16:18,230
You have just earned yourself a seat at the head table, pal.

899
01:16:18,400 --> 01:16:19,990
And we already got the tuxes.

900
01:16:31,370 --> 01:16:33,960
Boy, this party really died.

901
01:16:39,880 --> 01:16:42,510
Hey, maybe it was a coincidence.

902
01:16:42,680 --> 01:16:45,390
"Hey, maybe it was a coincidence."

903
01:16:45,550 --> 01:16:48,850
It was a message, Shay, pure and simple.

904
01:16:49,020 --> 01:16:53,520
I mean, we killed their bird. Now they killed one of ours.

905
01:16:56,020 --> 01:16:58,610
How could anybody whack a bird with a cork?

906
01:16:58,780 --> 01:17:01,360
These guys aren't just anybody.

907
01:17:01,530 --> 01:17:03,280
They're good.

908
01:17:09,700 --> 01:17:11,790
Mary Christmas.

909
01:17:12,660 --> 01:17:15,290
Mrs. Mary Christmas.

910
01:17:16,040 --> 01:17:17,960
Kind of catchy, huh, Har?

911
01:17:18,130 --> 01:17:19,920
Yeah, yeah, that sounds nice, Lloyd...

912
01:17:20,090 --> 01:17:23,170
but, don't you think you might be jumping the gun a little bit?

913
01:17:23,340 --> 01:17:24,840
I mean, you know.who knows?

914
01:17:25,010 --> 01:17:29,180
Maybe once you get to know her, you'll find out that she's not your type.

915
01:17:33,020 --> 01:17:37,020
Don't you ever say that again.

916
01:17:37,400 --> 01:17:39,520
She is the love of my life!

917
01:17:39,690 --> 01:17:41,780
The blood in my veins.

918
01:17:41,940 --> 01:17:43,740
we belong together!

919
01:17:43,900 --> 01:17:47,740
Till the mountains fall into the sea, till the heavens collide...

920
01:17:47,910 --> 01:17:51,660
or until I get sick of her and need to move on.You hear me?

921
01:17:51,830 --> 01:17:53,950
Okay, okay, okay. Lloyd, just calm down.

922
01:17:54,120 --> 01:17:56,000
Just calm down.

923
01:17:57,500 --> 01:17:59,130
Okay.

924
01:17:59,290 --> 01:18:01,050
Now.

925
01:18:02,460 --> 01:18:04,380
Let me get this straight.

926
01:18:04,720 --> 01:18:07,260
Lobby bar in the lobby.

927
01:18:07,430 --> 01:18:11,470
Yeah, that's what she said. She'll meet you there at 10:00 sharp.

928
01:18:12,350 --> 01:18:14,640
-Okay. -Okay.

929
01:18:17,100 --> 01:18:19,730
where you going in that getup?

930
01:18:20,770 --> 01:18:24,360
I just thought when, you know, you'd be off making your love connection...

931
01:18:24,530 --> 01:18:27,360
I'd be out, trying my luck on the slopes.

932
01:18:27,950 --> 01:18:31,580
You mean you're gonna go out in public dressed in tights?

933
01:18:31,740 --> 01:18:33,290
No, these aren't tights, Lloyd.

934
01:18:33,450 --> 01:18:36,410
These are fashionable Eurotrash ski trousers.

935
01:18:36,620 --> 01:18:38,210
Pretty revealing.

936
01:18:39,290 --> 01:18:40,290
Really?

937
01:18:40,460 --> 01:18:44,630
Yeah, but it's just a tiny lump. No one will notice.

938
01:18:45,550 --> 01:18:48,180
You're right. I can't go out dressed like this.

939
01:19:05,400 --> 01:19:07,610
Hey! Coming!

940
01:19:12,620 --> 01:19:15,160
Nice going, buddy.

941
01:19:30,720 --> 01:19:32,180
Ma'am.

942
01:19:36,020 --> 01:19:38,350
Beautiful outfit, sir.

943
01:19:40,020 --> 01:19:41,850
There you go.

944
01:19:53,370 --> 01:19:54,530
How you doing?

945
01:19:54,700 --> 01:19:58,290
You're a little early. we don't open for about 45 minutes.

946
01:19:59,330 --> 01:20:01,540
I'm meeting someone here.

947
01:20:02,380 --> 01:20:03,630
Mind if I wait at the bar?

948
01:20:03,790 --> 01:20:05,000
No, come on in.

949
01:20:08,630 --> 01:20:10,550
It's a beautiful day, huh, Harry?

950
01:20:10,720 --> 01:20:14,390
Yes, yes, I've had a wonderful time so far. Thank you.

951
01:20:14,970 --> 01:20:17,890
God, it feels so good to get up here.

952
01:20:18,060 --> 01:20:20,850
I haven't been outside that much in the last couple of weeks.

953
01:20:21,020 --> 01:20:22,850
Oh, yeah? why not?

954
01:20:24,150 --> 01:20:27,570
There's been some family problems...

955
01:20:27,730 --> 01:20:29,900
but I don't wanna bore you with those.

956
01:20:30,070 --> 01:20:31,610
Thanks.

957
01:20:32,820 --> 01:20:34,910
Oh, look. Frost.

958
01:20:38,540 --> 01:20:40,200
Harry?

959
01:20:43,580 --> 01:20:48,090
-Are you okay? -Oh, yeah. I just...I do this all the time.

960
01:21:02,390 --> 01:21:04,310
Hi there.

961
01:21:05,270 --> 01:21:07,150
Say, kids.

962
01:21:07,610 --> 01:21:10,940
You wouldn't happen to have a cup of warm water, would you?

963
01:21:17,910 --> 01:21:19,580
Excuse me.

964
01:21:20,200 --> 01:21:22,290
ls it 10 a.m.yet?

965
01:21:24,000 --> 01:21:25,580
It's 1.

966
01:21:27,670 --> 01:21:29,630
That's what I have too.

967
01:21:29,800 --> 01:21:31,420
I thought maybe it was fast.

968
01:21:35,470 --> 01:21:37,180
She's running late, huh?

969
01:21:37,350 --> 01:21:39,430
Just a couple hours.

970
01:21:39,600 --> 01:21:40,760
You know girls.

971
01:21:40,930 --> 01:21:43,390
when they're excited about something...

972
01:21:43,560 --> 01:21:46,440
everything has to be perfect.

973
01:21:54,240 --> 01:21:56,070
This one's on me.

974
01:21:57,620 --> 01:21:59,490
Yippee.

975
01:22:00,370 --> 01:22:02,290
Chablis, please.

976
01:22:03,250 --> 01:22:04,710
Hello.

977
01:22:11,170 --> 01:22:13,010
Bad day, huh?

978
01:22:14,340 --> 01:22:16,010
Me too.

979
01:22:16,470 --> 01:22:20,260
Of course, everything's been bad since I broke up with my boyfriend.

980
01:22:39,120 --> 01:22:40,200
My God.

981
01:22:40,370 --> 01:22:41,740
You poor guy. Does it hurt?

982
01:22:41,910 --> 01:22:45,580
Oh, no. I'm fine. I saved a seat for you.

983
01:22:45,830 --> 01:22:47,710
Oh, no. Listen, this is silly.

984
01:22:47,870 --> 01:22:49,670
-Let me help you. -No, no, no.

985
01:22:49,830 --> 01:22:52,040
It will only hurt for a moment, like a Band-Aid.

986
01:22:52,210 --> 01:22:53,920
-Come on, ready? -No, no, no.

987
01:22:54,090 --> 01:22:56,470
-No. -Come on. Go.

988
01:24:25,390 --> 01:24:27,930
Let go! Help! Help!

989
01:24:33,060 --> 01:24:36,150
Come on. Come on, come on.

990
01:24:43,910 --> 01:24:45,320
what am...?

991
01:24:49,540 --> 01:24:53,500
I said to myself, "Run, Beth.Run for your life before this man kills you both."

992
01:24:53,670 --> 01:24:55,790
Then do you know what the klutz did?

993
01:24:55,960 --> 01:24:59,300
No, and I don't care.

994
01:24:59,460 --> 01:25:02,170
I'm gonna tell you. He came home one night dead drunk...

995
01:25:02,340 --> 01:25:05,430
and decided he wanted to fix the sink. I couldn't believe him.

996
01:25:05,600 --> 01:25:08,850
Anyway, enough about me. Let's talk about you. How come you're here?

997
01:25:09,020 --> 01:25:10,520
-Bartender. -How come?

998
01:25:13,690 --> 01:25:16,770
You wouldn't happen to know a Mary Swanson, would you?

999
01:25:17,400 --> 01:25:18,690
Mary Swanson?

1000
01:25:18,860 --> 01:25:22,030
Yeah, she comes in here all the time.

1001
01:25:23,360 --> 01:25:25,700
-what's that supposed to mean? -She has dinner.

1002
01:25:28,660 --> 01:25:30,330
I'm sorry.

1003
01:25:35,210 --> 01:25:37,630
Do you know where she lives?

1004
01:25:38,380 --> 01:25:41,710
Yeah, her family has the big place up on Alpine Drive.

1005
01:25:42,220 --> 01:25:43,510
Alpine Drive?

1006
01:25:43,680 --> 01:25:45,380
Big place?

1007
01:25:53,060 --> 01:25:55,100
No way.

1008
01:25:56,600 --> 01:25:58,650
That's great.

1009
01:25:58,820 --> 01:26:00,860
we landed on the moon!

1010
01:26:08,410 --> 01:26:10,990
I've gotta tell you, today was just what I needed.

1011
01:26:11,160 --> 01:26:12,240
Thanks a lot, Harry.

1012
01:26:12,410 --> 01:26:14,370
Oh, it was...

1013
01:26:15,250 --> 01:26:17,750
It was my pleasure, Mary.

1014
01:26:18,250 --> 01:26:21,460
So you'll pick me up tonight at 7:45?

1015
01:26:21,800 --> 01:26:24,130
well, no. I got a few things to take care of first.

1016
01:26:24,300 --> 01:26:26,930
But why don't we make it quarter to 8?

1017
01:26:27,470 --> 01:26:29,510
Stop it.

1018
01:26:30,350 --> 01:26:32,890
Okay, 7:45.

1019
01:26:36,100 --> 01:26:37,690
Bye.

1020
01:27:22,070 --> 01:27:25,400
It doesn't make any sense, Lloyd. She told me 10:00 sharp.

1021
01:27:25,570 --> 01:27:27,690
Are you sure you went to the right bar?

1022
01:27:27,860 --> 01:27:30,530
Oh, yeah.Yeah.

1023
01:27:30,740 --> 01:27:32,620
I'm pretty sure.

1024
01:27:32,780 --> 01:27:34,950
Lobby bar, right in the lobby.

1025
01:27:38,460 --> 01:27:40,960
Maybe she just had a change of heart.

1026
01:27:41,580 --> 01:27:44,460
Oh, that pisses me off. That pisses me right off.

1027
01:27:44,630 --> 01:27:46,340
I hate when women do that, you know?

1028
01:27:46,510 --> 01:27:49,340
She wanted to see you again. She told me that.

1029
01:27:49,510 --> 01:27:52,300
And now, no? Now...wait a minute.wait.

1030
01:27:53,390 --> 01:27:55,970
She must have meant 10:00 at night.

1031
01:27:58,020 --> 01:27:59,020
Do you think?

1032
01:27:59,190 --> 01:28:02,440
why would she have you meet her at a bar at 10 in the morning?

1033
01:28:02,610 --> 01:28:04,690
I just figured she was a raging alcoholic.

1034
01:28:10,280 --> 01:28:11,320
Oh, that's the...

1035
01:28:11,490 --> 01:28:16,660
And all this time I've been going through such pain and personal anguish.

1036
01:28:16,830 --> 01:28:19,710
Such hell, for nothing.

1037
01:28:19,870 --> 01:28:23,540
Oh, God, that's funny. Oh, that's good stuff.

1038
01:28:23,710 --> 01:28:27,130
Oh, boy. well, looks like you got your night planned...

1039
01:28:27,300 --> 01:28:29,170
so I'm gonna head out, catch a flick.

1040
01:28:29,340 --> 01:28:30,380
Okay.

1041
01:28:33,220 --> 01:28:34,890
Ten in the morning.

1042
01:28:52,570 --> 01:28:54,870
Hey, Harry, old buddy, old pal.

1043
01:28:55,030 --> 01:28:56,580
Yeah?

1044
01:28:56,910 --> 01:28:59,580
will you join me in a good-luck toast before you head out?

1045
01:29:00,000 --> 01:29:02,460
Sure. whatever you think will help your chances.

1046
01:29:02,620 --> 01:29:05,420
Yes, sirree.

1047
01:29:07,000 --> 01:29:08,460
You know why I like you, Harry?

1048
01:29:08,630 --> 01:29:10,380
Because you're a regular guy.

1049
01:29:11,030 --> 01:29:11,730


1050
01:29:11,760 --> 01:29:12,760
Yep.

1051
01:29:12,930 --> 01:29:15,430
That's why I want you to stay regular.

1052
01:29:16,350 --> 01:29:20,470
One half-teaspoon for fast, effective relief.

1053
01:29:41,950 --> 01:29:44,410
To my friend, Harry...

1054
01:29:44,580 --> 01:29:45,620
the matchmaker.

1055
01:29:47,210 --> 01:29:50,130
Get out of here.I'm...I've...

1056
01:30:15,780 --> 01:30:18,700
Hi, the door's open.Come on upstairs.

1057
01:30:25,080 --> 01:30:27,710
Hi.Make yourself at home. I'm almost ready. One minute?

1058
01:30:27,880 --> 01:30:30,500
-Okay. Sounds good. -Okay.

1059
01:31:54,340 --> 01:31:56,760
Harry? Are you in there?

1060
01:31:58,090 --> 01:31:59,930
Be right out.

1061
01:32:00,300 --> 01:32:02,760
I hope you're not using the toilet. It's broken.

1062
01:32:05,260 --> 01:32:06,520
Huh?

1063
01:32:06,680 --> 01:32:09,060
The toilet doesn't flush.

1064
01:32:10,060 --> 01:32:11,900
No, I was just shaving.

1065
01:32:12,810 --> 01:32:13,940
Shaving?

1066
01:32:14,110 --> 01:32:19,190
Yeah, I was running a little late. I thought this would save some time.

1067
01:32:21,570 --> 01:32:22,990
Okay.

1068
01:32:23,160 --> 01:32:25,240
I'll be in the kitchen whenever you're ready.

1069
01:32:28,290 --> 01:32:30,160
Oh, jeez.

1070
01:32:46,140 --> 01:32:47,640
Tomorrow on A Current Affair...

1071
01:32:47,810 --> 01:32:50,480
inside the home of the Menendez brothers, attorney.

1072
01:32:50,640 --> 01:32:52,560
And next, we'll be back in a minute...

1073
01:32:52,730 --> 01:32:56,480
with the heartbreaking story of the bIind Rhode IsIand boy...

1074
01:32:56,650 --> 01:32:59,990
who was duped into buying a dead parakeet.

1075
01:33:00,150 --> 01:33:03,820
I just thought he was real quiet.

1076
01:33:07,990 --> 01:33:10,120
who are these sick people?

1077
01:33:17,590 --> 01:33:19,130
Yes?

1078
01:33:19,590 --> 01:33:20,630
Remember me?

1079
01:33:23,470 --> 01:33:24,970
Not really.

1080
01:33:26,100 --> 01:33:28,680
Providence. Providence.

1081
01:33:29,140 --> 01:33:31,140
I drove you to the airport last week.

1082
01:33:31,310 --> 01:33:33,600
Oh, my God.

1083
01:33:34,520 --> 01:33:35,600
Lloyd, right?

1084
01:33:36,650 --> 01:33:39,110
You remembered my name.

1085
01:33:40,070 --> 01:33:41,650
what are you doing in Aspen?

1086
01:33:41,820 --> 01:33:43,490
I brought you your briefcase.

1087
01:33:43,650 --> 01:33:46,910
You left it at the airport, you big goof.

1088
01:33:47,530 --> 01:33:49,200
-You have my briefcase? -Yeah.

1089
01:33:50,490 --> 01:33:52,370
Hey, I have it at my hotel room.

1090
01:33:52,540 --> 01:33:56,540
wanna jump on the bike with me? we can go get it.Unless....

1091
01:33:57,630 --> 01:33:59,290
Unless you're busy. I'll...

1092
01:33:59,460 --> 01:34:01,300
-Oh, no.No. -No...No, I don't wanna...

1093
01:34:01,460 --> 01:34:03,630
-You just wait right here, okay? -Okay.

1094
01:34:08,930 --> 01:34:11,720
Come on, flush, you bastard.

1095
01:34:15,730 --> 01:34:17,350
Harry, what are you doing in there?

1096
01:34:17,900 --> 01:34:22,570
Uh...Uh...I'm just...I'm cleaning my teeth.

1097
01:34:37,920 --> 01:34:39,170
Harry?

1098
01:34:39,340 --> 01:34:41,340
I'm gargling.

1099
01:34:41,500 --> 01:34:43,920
Just give me a minute, Mary. I'll be right with you.

1100
01:34:44,090 --> 01:34:48,550
Harry, I'm sorry, but something important has come up and I've got to run out.

1101
01:34:48,720 --> 01:34:51,100
It's sort of an emergency. I'll explain later.

1102
01:34:51,260 --> 01:34:53,430
-But, Mary... -I'm sorry, Harry.

1103
01:34:53,600 --> 01:34:56,890
I've really got to go. I promise we'll do this again sometime.

1104
01:35:08,950 --> 01:35:10,870
Race you to the top.

1105
01:35:13,620 --> 01:35:15,080
Come here.

1106
01:35:18,920 --> 01:35:21,000
Yeah!

1107
01:35:22,960 --> 01:35:24,630
I won.

1108
01:35:25,130 --> 01:35:27,260
Look familiar?

1109
01:35:27,630 --> 01:35:30,640
-I don't believe it.You really have it. -Of course I have it.

1110
01:35:30,800 --> 01:35:33,220
when Lloyd Christmas drives a woman to the airport...

1111
01:35:33,390 --> 01:35:36,470
he makes sure she gets her luggage. That's my whole philosophy.

1112
01:35:36,890 --> 01:35:38,140
This is incredible.

1113
01:35:38,310 --> 01:35:42,650
You mean to say you drove 2000 miles just for me?

1114
01:35:44,440 --> 01:35:50,070
I didn't really have a lot to do, you know...

1115
01:35:50,240 --> 01:35:53,160
and I know how frustrating it can be to lose a bag.

1116
01:35:55,160 --> 01:35:57,330
That is so sweet, Lloyd.

1117
01:36:12,260 --> 01:36:13,300
Look, Mary.

1118
01:36:13,470 --> 01:36:17,390
I know this may seem a little sudden but I've given it a lot of thought.

1119
01:36:17,560 --> 01:36:20,190
You're the woman I've been waiting for my whole life...

1120
01:36:20,350 --> 01:36:23,480
and I'm not ashamed to admit it. Please...

1121
01:36:24,230 --> 01:36:26,110
let me finish.

1122
01:36:27,990 --> 01:36:29,940
I'm crazy about you.

1123
01:36:30,110 --> 01:36:33,240
I've never felt this way about anybody.

1124
01:36:33,530 --> 01:36:38,700
Listen to me. I feel like a schoolboy again.

1125
01:36:39,410 --> 01:36:44,080
A schoolboy who desperately wants to make sweet, sweet love to you.

1126
01:36:55,050 --> 01:36:57,890
I thought I heard you talking to someone.

1127
01:36:59,560 --> 01:37:01,100
Mary.

1128
01:37:08,690 --> 01:37:11,070
I desperately wanna make love to a schoolboy.

1129
01:37:13,820 --> 01:37:15,490
-Maybe I should be going. -No, no.

1130
01:37:17,580 --> 01:37:19,120
No, I've...

1131
01:37:19,290 --> 01:37:21,410
That's not what I meant.

1132
01:37:25,750 --> 01:37:27,920
what I meant was...

1133
01:37:32,130 --> 01:37:35,050
I like you, Mary.

1134
01:37:38,930 --> 01:37:42,730
I like you a lot...

1135
01:37:43,440 --> 01:37:47,230
and I wanna ask you a question, straight out, flat out...

1136
01:37:47,400 --> 01:37:50,070
and I want you to give me the honest answer.

1137
01:37:50,690 --> 01:37:56,530
what do you think the chances are of a guy like you and a girl like me...

1138
01:37:58,410 --> 01:37:59,870
ending up together?

1139
01:38:00,620 --> 01:38:04,960
well, Lloyd, that's difficult to say. we really don't...

1140
01:38:05,120 --> 01:38:07,790
Hit me with it. Just give it to me straight.

1141
01:38:07,960 --> 01:38:10,800
I came a long way just to see you, Mary. Just...

1142
01:38:10,960 --> 01:38:12,880
The least you can do is level with me.

1143
01:38:13,050 --> 01:38:15,130
what are my chances?

1144
01:38:16,180 --> 01:38:17,220
Not good.

1145
01:38:22,180 --> 01:38:25,980
You mean "not good" like one out of a hundred?

1146
01:38:26,150 --> 01:38:31,020
I'd say...more like one out of a million.

1147
01:38:36,700 --> 01:38:40,160
So you're telling me there's a chance.

1148
01:38:42,240 --> 01:38:43,620
Yeah!

1149
01:38:45,960 --> 01:38:47,750
I read you.

1150
01:38:56,180 --> 01:38:57,720
we have plenty of towels. Thanks.

1151
01:38:57,890 --> 01:39:00,180
Nicholas. what are you doing here?

1152
01:39:00,350 --> 01:39:03,850
I've been looking for you, Mary. I have some news about your husband.

1153
01:39:05,310 --> 01:39:07,020
Husband?

1154
01:39:07,190 --> 01:39:09,310
wait a minute.

1155
01:39:10,110 --> 01:39:13,610
what was all that one-in-a-million talk?

1156
01:39:14,690 --> 01:39:17,360
Aren't you gonna invite me in?

1157
01:39:22,370 --> 01:39:25,200
Hey, Harry.You never called.

1158
01:39:26,210 --> 01:39:28,040
what are you doing here?

1159
01:39:31,920 --> 01:39:33,130
Excuse me, gunman.

1160
01:39:33,710 --> 01:39:36,630
-who are you? -Oh, don't play dumb with me, asshole.

1161
01:39:36,800 --> 01:39:40,510
I'm the rightful owner of that briefcase that you've been carrying around.

1162
01:39:40,800 --> 01:39:42,890
Oh, well, then.

1163
01:39:43,060 --> 01:39:45,890
Nicholas, my family trusted you.

1164
01:39:46,060 --> 01:39:47,560
Shut up.

1165
01:39:48,480 --> 01:39:51,850
Listen, Mr.Samsonite, about the briefcase.

1166
01:39:52,020 --> 01:39:55,570
My friend Harry and I have every intention of fully reimbursing you.

1167
01:39:56,740 --> 01:39:58,240
what are you talking about?

1168
01:39:58,570 --> 01:40:00,240
You open it up. Open it up.

1169
01:40:00,700 --> 01:40:02,070
Go ahead. Open it up.

1170
01:40:02,240 --> 01:40:03,910
Do what he says.

1171
01:40:04,080 --> 01:40:05,490
Hurry.

1172
01:40:10,750 --> 01:40:14,040
what is this? what is this? where's all the money?

1173
01:40:14,960 --> 01:40:16,800
That's as good as money, sir.

1174
01:40:16,960 --> 01:40:18,760
Those are lOU's.

1175
01:40:18,920 --> 01:40:21,760
Go ahead and add it up. Every cent's accounted for.

1176
01:40:21,930 --> 01:40:23,340
Look.

1177
01:40:23,680 --> 01:40:25,560
See this? That's a car.

1178
01:40:25,720 --> 01:40:28,930
Two hundred and seventy-five thou. Might wanna hang on to that one.

1179
01:40:33,270 --> 01:40:35,690
You're a dead man. You're a dead man!

1180
01:40:41,070 --> 01:40:42,200
Lloyd!

1181
01:40:42,360 --> 01:40:44,370
I'm home.

1182
01:40:44,780 --> 01:40:47,120
Look, we've gotta have a serious talk.

1183
01:40:47,290 --> 01:40:48,790
I got a confession to make.

1184
01:40:49,160 --> 01:40:52,540
Oh, good.You found her. I'll leave you two alone.

1185
01:40:52,710 --> 01:40:55,210
No, stay.

1186
01:41:01,880 --> 01:41:04,090
Yes, I'd like a one-way ticket to Amsterdam...

1187
01:41:04,260 --> 01:41:06,640
departing as soon as possible, please.

1188
01:41:06,810 --> 01:41:09,640
Okay, how do you guys know each other?

1189
01:41:09,810 --> 01:41:13,270
-we used to be best friends. -Yeah, until he turned into a backstabber.

1190
01:41:13,440 --> 01:41:16,230
Me a backstabber? You got a lot of nerve.

1191
01:41:16,400 --> 01:41:18,320
-You knew I was crazy about her. Yeah.

1192
01:41:18,480 --> 01:41:20,490
You knew I was crazy about Fraida Felcher...

1193
01:41:20,650 --> 01:41:22,740
and that didn't stop you, did it?

1194
01:41:24,530 --> 01:41:25,570
what do you mean?

1195
01:41:25,740 --> 01:41:27,700
"what do you mean?" Don't deny it, Lloyd.

1196
01:41:27,870 --> 01:41:31,120
Fraida told me the whole sleazy story, Mr.French Tickler.

1197
01:41:34,460 --> 01:41:37,250
Okay, what time does it...? what time does that leave?

1198
01:41:37,800 --> 01:41:39,500
Thank you. Hey, wait a second.

1199
01:41:39,670 --> 01:41:41,010
Can I have a vegetarian meal?

1200
01:41:41,420 --> 01:41:44,180
we both learned something about each other today, didn't we?

1201
01:41:44,340 --> 01:41:45,430
Yeah, you said it, pal.

1202
01:41:45,590 --> 01:41:48,350
-we're not as good friends as we thought. -Yeah, guess not.

1203
01:41:48,510 --> 01:41:51,220
I mean, if one beautiful girl can rip us apart like this...

1204
01:41:51,390 --> 01:41:54,850
then our friendship isn't worth a damn. we should call quits right now.

1205
01:41:55,020 --> 01:41:59,020
-You just tell me where to sign, bud. -Right on my ass, after you kiss it.

1206
01:41:59,190 --> 01:42:02,820
Kiss it? You kiss mine. Both cheeks, both lips, right here.

1207
01:42:04,610 --> 01:42:07,700
-Come on, come on.Put it right... -Shut up.

1208
01:42:08,700 --> 01:42:11,200
Now, which one of you losers wants to get it first?

1209
01:42:13,080 --> 01:42:14,500
Over here.

1210
01:42:15,710 --> 01:42:17,920
I was the one that got you into this whole mess.

1211
01:42:18,090 --> 01:42:20,040
Come on, shoot me.

1212
01:42:20,460 --> 01:42:22,170
No, wait.

1213
01:42:22,340 --> 01:42:23,710
wait, no, no. Do me first.

1214
01:42:23,880 --> 01:42:26,180
-I stole your girl. I deserve it. -No, you don't.

1215
01:42:26,340 --> 01:42:28,010
-Yes, I do. -No, you don't. No.

1216
01:42:28,180 --> 01:42:31,560
Yes, I do. Yesterday was one of the greatest days of my life.

1217
01:42:31,720 --> 01:42:35,810
Mary and I went skiing, we made a snowman, she touched my leg.

1218
01:42:35,980 --> 01:42:37,900
Okay, kill him.

1219
01:42:45,530 --> 01:42:47,160
Oh, no.

1220
01:42:48,990 --> 01:42:51,870
You killed my best friend, you bastard!

1221
01:42:52,040 --> 01:42:55,370
well, if it's any consolation, you're about to be reunited.

1222
01:43:01,550 --> 01:43:03,250
Harry.

1223
01:43:03,420 --> 01:43:06,010
You're alive!

1224
01:43:06,550 --> 01:43:08,380
And you're a horrible shot.

1225
01:43:09,640 --> 01:43:13,180
-Lucky me. -Police officers! Nobody move!

1226
01:43:13,350 --> 01:43:16,350
Everybody freeze! All right, get those hands up!

1227
01:43:16,520 --> 01:43:17,850
Not you, dummy.

1228
01:43:18,020 --> 01:43:19,600
-Get the gun. -Look out, look out.

1229
01:43:19,770 --> 01:43:22,190
Special Officer Beth Jordan, FBI.

1230
01:43:22,360 --> 01:43:24,690
Hey.who? But...Huh?

1231
01:43:24,860 --> 01:43:28,700
Mr.Dunne, thank you very much. we couldn't have done it without you.

1232
01:43:29,110 --> 01:43:31,780
we've been following you guys all the way from Providence.

1233
01:43:32,200 --> 01:43:34,450
what's going on, Harry?

1234
01:43:34,620 --> 01:43:37,040
Your name is Harry, isn't it?

1235
01:43:37,210 --> 01:43:40,290
Yeah, she grabbed me down in the lobby, explained what was up...

1236
01:43:40,460 --> 01:43:44,590
and then they slapped this bulletproof vest on me and gave me a gun.

1237
01:43:46,970 --> 01:43:48,760
But what if he shot you in the face?

1238
01:43:50,300 --> 01:43:52,430
what if he shot me in the face?

1239
01:43:52,600 --> 01:43:54,810
That's a risk we were willing to take.

1240
01:43:54,970 --> 01:43:56,890
How come I didn't get a gun?

1241
01:43:57,060 --> 01:43:58,980
Did you get a gun?

1242
01:44:27,170 --> 01:44:28,880
You were right, Lloyd.

1243
01:44:29,050 --> 01:44:31,470
She was definitely worth the trip.

1244
01:44:32,220 --> 01:44:33,680
Yeah.

1245
01:44:33,850 --> 01:44:36,180
She's something, ain't she, Har?

1246
01:44:36,350 --> 01:44:38,220
I'm glad we were able to help her out.

1247
01:44:48,030 --> 01:44:49,400
-Bobby. -Easy, easy.

1248
01:44:49,570 --> 01:44:53,320
-You're okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -I'm okay, I'm just a little sore.

1249
01:44:53,490 --> 01:44:57,330
-Oh, sweetie. -Oh, baby, I missed your loving.

1250
01:44:57,490 --> 01:44:59,450
There's someone I want to introduce you to.

1251
01:44:59,620 --> 01:45:02,870
He's kindest, gentlest man I've ever met. will you meet him?

1252
01:45:03,040 --> 01:45:04,040
-Sure. -Okay.

1253
01:45:04,210 --> 01:45:05,380
He's got a gun!

1254
01:45:08,880 --> 01:45:11,760
-Die! -Lloyd, Lloyd.

1255
01:45:13,470 --> 01:45:16,470
I said, this is my husband, Bobby.

1256
01:45:16,640 --> 01:45:19,560
-Oh. Hi, Bobby. -Hi.

1257
01:45:19,730 --> 01:45:22,390
I'm so happy for you.

1258
01:45:23,440 --> 01:45:27,020
Thank you.Thank you both very much.

1259
01:45:27,190 --> 01:45:31,110
I owe you both a debt of gratitude.

1260
01:45:31,530 --> 01:45:33,150
Thank you.

1261
01:45:51,510 --> 01:45:53,920
I can't believe this, Lloyd.

1262
01:45:54,090 --> 01:45:57,850
First, Mary dumps us, then the cops take our nest egg...

1263
01:45:58,010 --> 01:45:59,470
and then our hog breaks down.

1264
01:45:59,640 --> 01:46:03,310
Yeah.when are we ever gonna catch a break?

1265
01:46:17,240 --> 01:46:18,240
Hi, y'all.

1266
01:46:19,620 --> 01:46:20,620
Hey, guys.

1267
01:46:20,790 --> 01:46:24,290
we're going on a national bikini tour, and we're looking for two oil boys...

1268
01:46:24,460 --> 01:46:26,750
who can grease us up before each competition.

1269
01:46:31,760 --> 01:46:33,960
You are in luck.

1270
01:46:34,380 --> 01:46:39,800
There's a town about three miles that way. I'm sure you'll find a couple guys there.

1271
01:46:42,680 --> 01:46:45,100
-Okay, thanks. -Bye.

1272
01:46:53,990 --> 01:46:56,490
Do you realize what you've done?

1273
01:46:56,660 --> 01:46:59,490
-Hey, wait! -Lloyd!

1274
01:47:00,660 --> 01:47:02,660
Lloyd!

1275
01:47:10,670 --> 01:47:15,550
You'll have to excuse my friend. He's a little slow.

1276
01:47:16,260 --> 01:47:19,260
The town is back that way.

1277
01:47:31,020 --> 01:47:33,230
Two lucky guys are gonna be driving around...

1278
01:47:33,400 --> 01:47:36,490
with those girls for the next couple of months.

1279
01:47:36,650 --> 01:47:38,110
Yeah.

1280
01:47:38,280 --> 01:47:40,990
Don't worry, we'll catch our break too.

1281
01:47:41,160 --> 01:47:43,700
Just gotta keep our eyes open.

1282
01:47:43,870 --> 01:47:45,290
Yep.

1283
01:47:47,790 --> 01:47:49,290
You're it.

1284
01:47:49,540 --> 01:47:51,500
-You're it. -You're it. Quitsies.

1285
01:47:51,670 --> 01:47:56,460
-You're it. Anti-quitsies, double stamp. -You're it.Anti-quitsies, triple stamp.

1286
01:47:56,630 --> 01:47:58,340
-No erasies. -You can't triple stamp.

1287
01:47:58,510 --> 01:48:00,630
-Can't triple stamp a double stamp. -You can.

1288
01:48:00,800 --> 01:48:03,550
You can't triple stamp. Lloyd, you can't triple a double stamp.

1289
01:48:05,350 --> 01:48:07,640
You can't triple stamp. That's the rule. You can't triple.

1290
01:48:07,810 --> 01:48:13,190
You can't triple stamp a double stamp, Lloyd. Lloyd! Lloyd!
