Paramount News
brings you special coverage
of Princess Ann's visit to London.
The first stop on her much publicised
goodwill tour of European capitals.
She gets a royal welcome.
Thousands cheer a young member of
one of Europe's oldest ruling families.
After three days of continuous activity
and a visit to Buckingham Palace,
Ann flew to Amsterdam,
where she dedicated
the new lnternational Aid Building
and an ocean liner.
Then she went to Paris,
attending many official functions
to cement trade relations
between her country
and the Western European nations.
And so to Rome, the Eternal City,
where the princess's visit
was marked by a spectacular parade,
highlighted by the band
of the crack bersaglieri regiment.
The smiling young princess
showed no sign
of the strain of the week's
continuous public appearances.
At her country's
embassy that evening,
a formal reception
and ball in her honour
was given by her country's
ambassador to ltaly.
Her Royal Highness.
His Excellency, the Papal Nuncio,
Monsignor Altomonte.
Sir Hugo Macey de Farmington.
- Good evening, Sir Hugo.
- Good evening, Your Highness.
His Highness, the Maharajah
of Khanipur, and the Raikuuari.
l'm so glad you could come.
Thank you, madam.
Friherre Erick af
Massinsjarna-Bergenskiold.
Prince lstvar Barlossy Nagayavaros.
How do you do?
Der Fürst und die Fürstin
von und zu Lucktenstichenholz.
Sir Hari Singh and Kmark Singh.
The Count and Countess
von Marstrand.
Good evening, Countess.
Good evening.
Senhor e senhora
Joao de Cam?es.
Good evening.
Hassan El Din Pasha.
How do you do?
l hate this nightgown.
l hate all my nightgowns,
and l hate all my underwear too.
- My dear, you have lovely things.
- But l'm not 200 years old.
- Why can't l sleep in pyjamas?
- Pyjamas!
Just the top part.
Did you know there are people
who sleep with absolutely nothing on?
l rejoice to say l did not.
Listen.
Oh, and your slippers.
Please put on your slippers
and come away from the window.
- Your milk and crackers.
- Everything we do is so wholesome.
They'll help you to sleep.
l'm too tired to sleep.
l shan't sleep a wink.
Now, my dear, if you don't mind,
tomorrow's schedule,
if that's your preferred
pronunciation, both are correct.
8.30, breakfast with
the embassy staff.
9 o'clock, leave for the
Polinari Automotive Works,
to be presented with a small car.
- Thank you.
- Which you won't accept.
- No, thank you.
- 1 0.35,
inspect agriculture organisation,
who'll present you with an olive tree.
- No, thank you.
- Which you will accept.
Thank you.
1 0.55, the new Foundling
Home for orphans.
Laying of cornerstone,
same speech as last Monday.
- Trade relations.
- Yes.
- For the orphans?
- Oh no, the other one.
- Youth and progress.
- Precisely.
1 1 .45, back here to rest.
No, that's wrong. 1 1 .45,
conference here with the press.
Sweetness and decency.
One o'clock sharp,
lunch with foreign ministry.
You'll wear white lace
and carry a bouquet
of very small pink roses.
- 3.05, presentation of a plaque.
- Thank you.
- 4.1 0, review special guard of police.
- No, thank you.
- 4.45, back here to change...
- How do you do? Charmed...
Stop!
Stop, stop!
- lt's all right, dear, it didn't spill.
- l don't care if it spilled or not.
My dear, you're ill.
l'll send for Doctor Bannochhoven.
l don't want him.
Please let me die in peace.
- You're not dying.
- Leave me!
lt's nerves. Control yourself, Ann.
l don't want to.
Your Highness!
- l'll get Doctor Bannochhoven.
- lt's no use.
l'll be dead before he gets here.
- She's asleep.
- She was in hysterics 3 minutes ago.
- Are you asleep, ma'am?
- No.
l'll only disturb Your Royal
Highness a moment.
l'm very ashamed, Doctor.
Suddenly l was crying.
To cry is perfectly normal.
lt's important she be calm and
relaxed for the press conference.
Don't worry, Doctor,
l'll be calm and relaxed.
l'll bow and l'll smile,
l'll improve trade relations and l'll...
There she goes again.
Give her something, please.
Uncover her arm, please.
- What's that?
- Sleep and calm.
This will relax you
and make you feel a little happy.
lt's a new drug, quite harmless.
There.
l don't feel any different.
You will. lt may take
a little time to take hold.
Just now, lie back.
- Can l keep just one light on?
- Of course.
The best thing l know is to do
exactly what you wish for a while.
Thank you, Doctor.
Oh, the General! Doctor, quick.
l'm perfectly all right.
Goodnight, ma'am.
- Goodnight, ma'am.
- Goodnight, Doctor.
- Bet five hundred.
- Five hundred. How many?
One.
- l'll take one.
- Three.
Four.
Two for Papa.
- 500 more.
- Without looking.
500, and l'll raise you 1 ,000.
- Two pairs.
- l've got three shy little sevens.
A nervous straight.
Come home, you fools.
Look at that, 6,500.
Not bad, that's ten bucks.
One more round and l'm gonna throw
you gents right out in the snow.
l gotta get up early.
A date with Her Highness, who'll
graciously pose for some pictures.
What do you mean early?
My personal invitation says 1 1 .45.
Could it be because you're ahead?
- lt could.
- Works out fine for me.
This is my last 5,000 and
you hyenas are not gonna get it.
Thanks, lrving.
See you at Ann's in the morning.
- Ciao, Joe.
- Stay sober.
All right, a little seven-card stud.
So happy.
How are you this evening?
Hey, hey.
- Wake up.
- Thank you very much.
- No, thank you.
Charmed.
Charmed too.
You may sit down.
You'd better sit up, or you'll
get picked up by the police.
- Police?
- Yes.
2.1 5 and back here to change.
2.45...
You know, people who can't
handle liquor shouldn't drink it.
''lf l were dead and buried
and l heard your voice,''
''beneath the sod my heart of dust
would still rejoice.''
Do you know that poem?
Whadda ya know?
You're well read, well dressed,
snoozing away in a public street.
Would you care to make a statement?
What the world needs
is a return to sweetness and decency
in the souls of its young men and...
Yeah, l couldn't agree
with you more, but...
Get yourself some coffee,
you'll be all right.
Look, you take the cab.
Come on, climb in
the cab and go home.
- So happy.
- Got any money?
- Never carry money.
- That's a bad habit.
All right. l'll drop you off, come on.
- lt's a taxi!
- lt's not the Super Chief.
Where are we going?
- Where do you live?
- What?
- Colosseum.
- Come on, you're not that drunk.
You're so smart, l'm not drunk at all.
- l'm just being very happy.
- Hey, don't go to sleep again.
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
Where shall l take you?
Where do you live?
Come on. Where do you live?
Come on, where do you live?
Colosseum.
- She lives in the Colosseum.
- lt's the wrong address.
Look, for me it is very late night.
My wife... l have three bambino,
you know bambino?
My taxi go home,
we go home together.
Via Margutta 51 .
Via Margutta 51 !
Here is Via Margutta 51 .
l am very happy.
A thousand lire. Mila lire.
One, two, three, four mila.
- OK.
- For me?
OK. Now, look,
take a little bit of that.
Take her wherever she wants to go.
Goodnight.
Oh! No, no. Momento.
All right. Look, when she wakes up,
she'll tell you where to go.
Momento.
My taxi is not for sleep.
You understand?
Look, pal, this is not my problem.
l never see her before. OK.
ls not your problem,
is not my problem.
What you want?
You don't want girl, me don't want girl.
Police. Maybe she want girl!
Stay calm, stay calm. OK.
So happy.
l ought to have my head examined.
ls this the elevator?
lt's my room!
l'm terribly sorry to mention it,
but the dizziness is getting worse.
- Can l sleep here?
- That's the general idea.
Can l have a silk nightgown
with rosebuds on it?
l'm afraid
you'll have to rough it tonight.
- ln these.
- Pyjamas.
Sorry, honey, l haven't
worn a nightgown in years.
Will you help me
get undressed, please?
OK.
There you are.
You can handle the rest.
May l have some?
No!
- Now, look!
- This is very unusual.
l've never been alone with a man
before, even with my dress on.
With my dress off, it's most unusual.
l don't seem to mind. Do you?
l think l'll go out for a cup of coffee.
You'd better get to sleep.
Oh, no. On this one.
You're terribly nice.
Hey, come here.
These are pyjamas, they're
to sleep in. You're to climb into them.
- Understand?
- Thank you.
And you sleep on the couch. Not on
the bed, on the couch. ls that clear?
- Do you know my favourite poem?
- You've already recited it.
''Arethusa arose
From her couch of snows''
''ln the Acroceraunian Mountains.''
- Keats.
- Shelley.
Keep your mind off the poetry
and on the pyjamas.
- You'll be fine.
- Keats.
Shelley. l'll be back
in about ten minutes.
Keats.
You have my permission to withdraw.
Thank you very much.
- Well?
- No trace.
- Did you search the grounds?
- Attics to cellar.
You must swear not to
speak of this to anyone.
l must remind you that the princess
is the direct heir to the throne.
This must be classified as top
crisis secret. Have l your pledge?
- Yes, sir.
- Very well.
Now we must notify Their Majesties.
- So happy.
- The pleasure's mine.
Screwball!
Holy smoke,
the princess's interview!
Eleven forty-five!
Oh, sh!
Hi, Joe.
- Morning, Joe.
- Hello, honey.
Mr Hennessy has been
looking for you.
Uh-oh.
Thanks a lot, hon.
Come in.
- Looking for me?
- Just coming to work?
- Who, me?
- We start at 8.30 in this office.
- We pick up our assignments...
- l got mine last night.
- What assignment was that?
- The princess, 1 1 .45.
You've already been to the interview?
Sure, l just got back.
- Well, well. All my apologies.
- lt's all right.
- lnteresting.
- No, just routine.
Did she answer
all the questions on the list?
Of course. l've got 'em
right here somewhere.
Don't disturb yourself,
l have a copy here.
How did Her Highness react to
the idea of a European Federation?
- She thought it was just fine.
- She did?
- She thought there'd be two effects.
- Two?
- The direct and the indirect.
- Remarkable.
Naturally, she thought that the indirect
would not be as direct as the direct.
- That is, not right away.
- No.
Later on, of course, nobody knows.
Well, well.
That was a shrewd observation.
They fool you, these royal kids.
They're smarter than we suspect.
How did she feel about
the future friendship of nations?
Youth. She felt that
the youth of the world
must lead the way to a better world.
Original.
By the way, what was she wearing?
- You mean what did she have on?
- That's usually what it means.
- ls it too warm for you?
- No, l just hurried over here.
Naturally, with a story
of these dimensions.
- Did you say she was wearing grey?
- No, l didn't.
- She usually wears grey.
- Well, it was a kind of a grey.
l think l know the dress,
it has a gold collar...
That's the one. l didn't know
exactly how to describe it.
l think you described it very well,
in view of the fact that
she was taken violently ill at 3 a.m.,
put to bed with a high fever,
and has had all her appointments
for today cancelled in toto!
- ln toto?
- Yes, Mr Bradley, in toto.
- That's pretty hard to swallow.
- ln view of the fact you just left her.
Here it is, Mr Bradley, all over the
front page of every paper in Rome.
All right, l overslept.
lt can happen to anybody.
lf you ever got up
and read a morning paper,
you might discover little news events,
little items of general interest,
that might stop you getting
immersed in such a gold-plated,
triple-decked, star-spangled
lie as you have just told me.
lf l were you l'd try some other
business, like mattress testing!
- ls this the princess?
- Yes, Mr Bradley.
lt isn't Annie Oakley, Dorothy Lamour
or Madame Chiang Kai-Shek.
Take a good look. You might
interview her again some day.
Am l fired?
No. When l want to fire you,
you won't have to ask.
You'll know you're fired.
The man's mad.
Giovanni, it's Joe Bradley.
Now listen carefully.
Hurry up to my place and see
if there's somebody there, asleep.
Aha. Si, Mr Joe.
l look, you wait.
- Mr Joe?
- Yeah. Tell me.
Giovanni, l love you! Now listen.
Yes, Mr Joe.
A gun? No.
Yes, a gun, a knife, anything.
But nobody goes in
and nobody goes out.
OK.
You still here?
What would a real interview
with this dame be worth?
- Are you referring to Her Highness?
- l'm not referring to Annie Oakley...
- How much?
- What do you care?
- You've got no chance...
- lf l did, how much?
Just a plain talk on world
conditions might be worth 250.
Her views on clothes, a lot more.
- Maybe 1 ,000.
- Dollars?
l'm talking about
her views on everything.
The private and secret
longings of a princess.
Her innermost thoughts, as revealed
to your own correspondent,
in a private, personal,
exclusive interview.
Can't use it, huh?
l didn't think you'd like it.
Come here.
- Love angle too, l suppose?
- Practically all love angle.
With pictures?
Could be. How much?
That particular story would be worth
five grand to any news service.
But tell me, Mr Bradley,
if you are sober,
how you are going to
obtain this fantastic interview.
l'll enter her sick room
disguised as a thermometer.
You said five grand?
l want you to shake on that.
You realise she's in bed
and leaves for Athens tomorrow?
- Yes.
- l'd like to make a little side bet.
Five hundred says
you don't come up with the story.
- What are you looking at that for?
- Just want to see what day it is.
- lt's a deal.
- Now l'd like you to shake.
You're into me for about $500 now.
When you lose this bet,
you'll owe me $1 ,000.
You poor sucker,
l'll practically own you.
You practically have for a couple
of years but that's all over.
l'm going to win that money and buy
a one-way ticket back to New York.
Go on, l love to hear you whine.
When l'm back in a real
newsroom, l'll think of you,
sitting here with an empty leash
and nobody to twitch for you.
So long, pigeon.
- Signor Bradley.
- Everything OK, Giovanni?
Si Signor Joe.
Nobody come, nobody go.
- Absolutely nobody.
- Swell, thanks a lot.
Oh... Giovanni...
How'd you like to make some money?
- Money?
- Yeah.
That's the stuff. l've got a sure thing.
- Double your money back in two days.
- Double my money?
l need a little investment
capital to swing the deal.
Now if you'll lend me a little cash...
You owe me two months rent
and you want me to lend you money?
No.
Tomorrow you'll be sorry.
Your Highness...?
Your Royal Highness...?
Yes, what is it?
Dear Dr Bannochhoven...
Oh, sure, yes, well...
You're fine, much better.
ls there anything you want?
- So many things.
- Yes? Well, tell the doctor.
Tell the good doctor everything.
l dreamt and l dreamt...
Yes? Well, what did you dream?
l dreamt l was asleep in the street,
and a young man came,
he was tall and strong.
He was so mean to me.
He was?
lt was wonderful.
Good morning.
- Where's Dr Bannochhoven?
- l'm afraid l don't know him.
- Wasn't l talking to him just now?
- Afraid not.
Have l had an accident?
No.
Quite safe for me to sit up, huh?
Perfectly.
Thank you.
Are these yours?
- Did you lose something?
- No.
Would you be so kind
as to tell me where l am?
This is what is laughingly
known as my apartment.
- Did you bring me here by force?
- No, no. Quite the contrary.
- Have l been here all night...alone?
- lf you don't count me, yes.
So l've spent the night here with you?
Well, l don't know that
l'd use those words exactly,
but from a certain angle, yes.
- How do you do?
- And you are?
- Bradley, Joe Bradley.
- Delighted.
- You don't know how delighted l am.
- You may sit down.
- Thank you very much.
What's your name?
- You may call me Anya.
- Well thank you, Anya.
- Coffee?
- What time is it?
About one-thirty.
One-thirty! l must get dressed and go!
Why the hurry? There's lots of time.
No there isn't, and l've been
enough trouble as it is.
Trouble?
You're not what l'd call trouble.
- l'm not?
- l'll run a bath for you.
There you are.
Here we go now.
There you are, that does it. All right.
Give me a little slack, will you?
lrving! Why don't you answer?
lt's Joe. Can you
get here in five minutes?
No, l can't come now, Joe, l'm busy.
Oh, no.
Joe, l'm up to my ears in work.
Get into your next outfit.
What kind of a scoop, Joe?
l can't talk over the phone.
This whole thing
might easily blow sky-high.
lt's front-page stuff,
that's all l can say.
lt might be political or
a scandal, l don't know,
but it's a big story.
l need pictures.
But l can't come now, Joe, l'm busy.
And l'm meeting Francesca
at Rocca's in half an hour.
- Don't understand.
- Don't understand?
There you are.
l was looking at all the people.
lt must be fun to live in a place like this.
lt has its moments. l can give you
a commentary on each apartment.
l must go.
- l only waited to say goodbye.
- Goodbye? But we've only just met!
- How about breakfast?
- l haven't time.
lt must be a pretty important date
to run off without eating.
- lt is.
- l'll go with you.
That's all right, l can find the place.
Thank you for letting me
sleep in your bed.
- That's all right. Think nothing of it.
- lt was very considerate of you.
You must've been awfully
uncomfortable on that couch.
No, l do it all the time.
- Goodbye, Mr Bradley.
- Goodbye.
Go right through there,
and down all the steps.
Thank you.
- Well... Small world!
- Yeah.
l almost forgot.
Can you lend me some money?
Oh, yeah.
That's right,
you didn't have any did you?
How much was it you wanted?
l don't know. How much have you got?
Suppose we just split this fifty-fifty.
Here's a thousand lire.
A thousand!
Can you really spare all that?
- lt's about a dollar and a half.
- Oh.
l'll arrange for it to be sent back to you.
What is your address?
Via Margutta 51 .
Joe Bradley.
Goodbye. Thank you.
Double my money, eh?
You tell me how?
- Tomorrow.
- Yes, tomorrow.
What a wonderful hair you have.
- Just cut, thank you.
- Just cut?
- Well, then... Cut so?
- Higher.
- Higher? Here?
- More.
- Here!
- Even more.
Where?
- There.
- Are you sure, Miss?
- l'm quite sure, thank you.
- All off?
- All off.
Off!
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
Yes!
Off!
Oh no, no.
That's a nice camera
you have there. Nice...
You don't mind if l borrow it?
- Miss Webber.
- Just for two minutes.
No.
Go, it's my camera.
You musician, maybe?
You artist, huh?
Painter?
l know. You model.
- Model, huh?
- Thank you.
lt's perfect.
You're nice without long hair.
Now it's cool, huh? Cool.
lt's just what l wanted.
Now, why don't you
come dancing tonight with me?
You should see, it's so nice.
lt's on a boat, on the Tiber,
the river, by Sant'Angelo.
Moonlight, music, romantic.
lt's very, very...
- Please, you come?
- l wish l could.
But your friends,
l don't think they'll recognise you.
No, l don't think they will.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
After nine l'll be there, dancing on
the river. Remember Sant'Angelo.
All my friends... lf you come,
you will be most pretty of all girls.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
A thousand lire.
- No money.
- No?
l'm sorry, l've really no money.
Look.
l'm sorry.
- Well, it's you!
- Yes, Mr Bradley.
Or is it?
- Do you like it?
- Very much.
So that was your
mysterious appointment.
- l have a confession to make.
- A confession?
Yes, l ran away
last night...from school.
Why?
- Trouble with the teacher?
- No, nothing like that.
You wouldn't run away for nothing.
lt was only meant to be
for a few hours.
They gave me something
last night to make me sleep.
Oh, l see.
- l'd better get a taxi and go back.
- Look, before you do,
why not take a little time for yourself?
Maybe another hour.
Live dangerously, take the whole day.
l could do some things
l've always wanted to.
Like what?
You can't imagine. l'd like to do
whatever l liked, the whole day long.
Like having your hair cut
and eating gelati?
Yes, and l'd like to
sit at a sidewalk café,
look in shop windows,
walk in the rain.
Have fun, and maybe
some excitement.
lt doesn't seem much to you,
does it?
lt's great.
Tell you what. Why don't we
do all those things...together?
- Don't you have to work?
- No. Today will be a holiday.
You don't want to do
a lot of silly things.
Don't l? First wish, one sidewalk café.
Coming right up.
l know just the place.
What will they say in school
about your hair?
They'll have a fit.
What would they say if they knew
l'd slept in your room?
Tell you what, you don't tell your folks
and l won't tell mine.
lt's a pact.
- Now, what would you like to drink?
- Champagne, please.
Champagne?
Well, champagne,
and cold coffee for me.
Must be quite a school,
champagne for lunch.
- Only on special occasions.
- For instance?
The last time
was my father's anniversary.
- Wedding?
- No.
The fortieth anniversary
of...the day he got his job.
Forty years on the job.
What do you know about that?
What does he do?
Well, mostly you might
call it public relations.
Oh, well that's hard work.
- l wouldn't care for it.
- Does he?
l've heard him complain about it.
Why doesn't he quit?
People in that line of work
almost never do quit,
unless it's actually unhealthy
for them to continue.
Well, here's to his health then.
You know, that's what
everybody says.
- lt's all right?
- Yes, thank you.
What is your work?
Oh, l'm in the selling game.
Really? How interesting.
What do you sell?
Fertiliser. Chemicals, stuff like that.
- lrving! Am l glad to see you!
- Why, did you forget your wallet?
- Sit down.
- Aren't you going to introduce me?
Yes. This is a very good friend of
mine, lrving Radovich. Anya, lrving.
- Anya...?
- Smith.
- Oh. Hiya, Smitty.
- Charmed.
Hey, did anybody ever tell you
you're a dead ringer for...
- Well, l guess l'll be going.
- No, don't do that, join us.
Well, just till Francesca gets here.
Tell me Mr Radovich,
what is a ringer?
- Oh, waiter!
- lt's an American term.
lt means anyone who has
a great deal of charm.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Cousins.
Mr Bradley's just been telling me
all about his work.
- l'd like to have heard that.
- What do you do?
l'm in the same racket as Joe,
only l'm a...
l'm awfully sorry, lrving.
- What are you...?
- l'm sorry.
l can take a hint. l'll see you around.
- But your drink's just here.
- Yeah, lrving, take it easy.
l'm sorry about that.
Sit down, that's a good fellow.
That's the boy.
You're... You're twisting
my arm, you know.
Just be a little more careful not to spill.
- Spill? Who's been spilling?
- You.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Where did you find this loony?
You're OK. Here's to you, huh?
Here's hoping for the best.
lf it wasn't for that hair,
l'd swear that you...
Thanks.
You slipped, you almost hurt yourself.
- l slipped?
- Yes, you did.
- l didn't slip.
- A bad sprain...
- Never mind!
- You'd better get it fixed up.
- Would you excuse us?
- Of course, l'm so sorry.
Joe, what are you trying to do?
Take your hands off me.
- Got your lighter?
- What?
- Have you?
- Yeah.
Listen, what would you do
for five grand?
- Five grand?
- Look...
She doesn't know who l am.
This is my story, l gotta protect it.
She's really the...
Your pictures
will make this twice as valuable.
- The princess goes slumming.
- You're in for 25%.
- Of 5,000?
- Minimum, Hennessy shook on it.
- That's $1 ,500!
- lt's $1 ,250.
- Now you shake.
- OK, now lend me 30,000.
That's $50! Are you gonna buy
the crown jewels?
She's drinking champagne.
We gotta entertain her.
We can't go running around
with a hot princess!
Do you want in
on this deal or don't you?
- This l want back Saturday.
- OK. Now where's your lighter?
Let's go to work.
- Better now?
- Huh?
- Your ear.
- My ear?
Oh, yeah, Joe fixed it.
- Would you like a cigarette?
- Yes, please.
You won't believe it,
but it's my very first.
Your very first?
- No smoking in school?
- Your first cigarette.
There, the gismo works.
Well, what's the verdict, OK?
- Nothing to it.
- That's right, nothing to it.
l'll stretch my legs a little.
- l'll pick this one up, lrving.
- You can afford it.
What next?
Shall we make a little schedule?
Oh, not that word, please.
l didn't mean a work schedule...
a school schedule,
- l meant a fun schedule.
- Let's just go, huh?
How about you, lrving, are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Francesca. Oh, this is...
- Smitty.
- She's a grand girl, lrving.
Five grand.
- Joe.
- Where are you going now?
Honey, l gotta work.
l'll call you tonight.
Look at those men! They were
supposed to be inconspicuous.
You asked for plain clothes.
Hey, stop, come back.
l'm going straight from now on.
News Service? What did he mean?
Oh, you say you're with the press
and you can get away with anything.
Going to church to get married
on a scooter! Joe's a wonderful liar.
Congratulations!
Don't look so worried,
l won't hold you to it.
Thank you very much.
Don't be too grateful.
OK, l won't.
l'm a good liar too, aren't l?
- The best l ever met.
- Thank you very much.
Say... Come with me.
The Mouth of Truth.
The legend is, if you're a liar
and you put your hand in there,
it'll be bitten off.
- What a horrid idea.
- Let's see you do it.
Let's see you do it.
Sure.
Hello!
- You beast, you're all right!
- l'm sorry. lt was just a joke.
- You never hurt your hand.
- l'm sorry.
- OK?
- Yes.
All right, let's go. Look out!
l'll park at the corner.
What do they mean,
all these inscriptions?
Each one represents a wish fulfilled.
lt started during the war, in an air raid.
A man with his four children
was caught in the street.
He ran to that wall for shelter
and prayed.
Bombs fell very close
but no one was hurt.
Later, he came back
and put up the first tablet.
Now it's a sort of shrine.
People come,
and when their wishes are granted,
they put up another plaque.
Lovely story.
Read some of the inscriptions.
Make a wish? Tell the doctor?
Anyway, the chances of it
being granted are very slight.
Well, what now?
- l've heard you can dance on a boat.
- You mean Sant'Angelo.
- Couldn't we go tonight?
- Why not?
Anything you wish.
At midnight l'll turn into a pumpkin
and drive away in my glass slipper.
That'll be the end of the fairytale.
- l guess lrving has to go now.
- l do?
Yes, you know, that big business
development you have to attend to?
- That development.
- Can't afford not to.
Yeah. See you later, Smitty.
- Good luck with the big development.
- Thanks.
Hello.
Mr Bradley, if you don't mind my
saying so, l think you're a ringer.
A what? Oh, thanks very much.
You've spent the whole day doing
things l've always wanted to. Why?
lt seemed the thing to do.
l've never heard of anybody so kind.
lt wasn't any trouble.
Or so completely unselfish.
Let's have a drink at the bar.
There you are.
l look for you a long time.
l think maybe you not come.
- Off, all off!
- lt's nice without, isn't it? Cool.
- Oh, very good.
- This is Mr Bradley.
l Mario Delani.
- Old friends?
- Yes, he cut my hair.
He invited me here tonight.
- What was your name?
- Mario Delani.
Mario Delani.
l'm very glad to know you.
Me too.
Oh, may l enjoy myself the pleasure?
- You mind?
- Go right ahead.
l thank you.
- Did l miss anything?
- You're just in time.
- Who's Smitty dancing with?
- Her barber.
He cut her hair this afternoon,
made a date for tonight.
The princess and the barber?
- What is it?
- Momento.
August!
Thank you.
Bye.
Your Highness.
Dance quietly towards the entrance.
A car is waiting.
- No.
- Your Highness!
You've made a mistake. Let me go!
Will you let me go? Mr Bradley!
Let me go, will you! Mr Bradley!
Hit him again, Smitty!
- Here are my car keys.
- Police!
The other side of the bridge.
- All right?
- Fine, you?
Oh, fine.
You were great back there.
You weren't so bad yourself.
l...
l guess we'd better get out of here.
This is the American Hour,
continuing our programme
of musical selections.
- Everything ruined?
- No. They'll be dry in a minute.
Suits you. You should
always wear my clothes.
Seems l do.
l thought a little wine might be good.
- Shall l cook something?
- No kitchen.
- l always eat out.
- Do you like that?
Well, life isn't always what one likes.
- ls it?
- No, it isn't.
- Tired?
- A little.
- You've had quite a day.
- A wonderful day.
This is the American Hour
with a special news bulletin.
There is no further word
from the bedside of Princess Ann,
who was taken ill yesterday
on the last leg of her European tour.
Rumours suggest
her condition may be serious,
causing alarm and anxiety
among the people in her country.
- The news can wait.
- Yes.
May l have a little more wine?
l'm sorry l couldn't
cook us some dinner.
Did you learn how in school?
l'm a good cook.
l could earn my living at it.
l can sew too, clean a house, iron.
l learned to do all those things,
l just haven't had the chance
to do it for anyone.
Well, looks like l'll have to move
and get a place with a kitchen.
Yes.
l shall have to go now.
Anya...
...there's something l want to tell you.
No, please.
Nothing.
l must go and get dressed.
Stop at the next corner, please.
OK.
- Here?
- Yes.
l have to leave you now.
l'm going to that
corner there and turning.
You stay in the car and drive away.
Promise not to watch me
go beyond the corner.
Just drive away and leave me.
As l leave you.
All right.
l don't know how to say goodbye.
l can't think of any words.
Don't try.
Your Royal Highness,
twenty-four hours,
they can't all be blank.
They are not.
What explanation am l
to offer Their Majesties?
l was indisposed. l am better.
Ma'am, you must appreciate
that l have my duty to perform,
just as Your Royal
Highness has her duty.
Your Excellency,
l trust you will not find it necessary
to use that word again.
Were l not completely aware of
my duty to my family and my country,
l would not have come back tonight.
Or indeed, ever again.
And now, since l understand
we have a very full schedule today,
you have my permission to withdraw.
No milk and crackers.
That will be all thank you, Countess.
- Did you really get it?
- What?
The princess exclusive.
Did you get it?
- No, l didn't.
- What? That's impossible.
- Coffee?
- Don't hold out on me.
- Who's holding out?
- You are. l know too much.
First you ask about an exclusive
on the princess, next you disappear.
Then l hear a rumour from the
embassy that she's out on the town.
Do you believe every rumour
that comes your way?
There's a lot of other rumours.
About a shindig down by the river,
and the arrest of eight secret
service men from a certain country.
Then she makes
a miraculous recovery. lt all adds up.
Don't think you'll raise the price,
a deal's a deal. Now come on.
- Where is that story?
- l have no story.
- Now what was the idea...
- Joe.
- Wait till you see these.
- lrving.
Hi, Mr Hennessy.
lrving!
- What's the idea?
- You charge in, spilling things!
- Me?
- l warned you before.
- Remember?
- Look at my pants.
- Come and dry them off.
- Nuts to that.
- Did you tell him about Smitty?
- Who?
- Wait till you...
- lrving!
There you go again, lrving.
- Joe...
- Save that till later.
- Why don't you go home and shave?
- Shave?
Or else keep quiet
till we're finished talking.
What kind of routine is that?
What are you up to? Who's Smitty?
- A guy we met.
- What is there to look at?
Just some of lrving's dames.
You wouldn't like them.
- Maybe you would.
- Don't change the subject.
- Yesterday you said...
- l had a good lead.
But l was wrong, that's all
there is to it. There is no story.
OK.
She's holding the press interview
today. Maybe you can get that story.
And you owe me $500.
- Take it from my salary, $50 a week.
- Don't think l won't.
What gives?
Have we had a better offer?
lrving...
l don't know just how
to tell you this, but...
Wait till l sit down.
Well, in regard to the story
that goes with these,
there is no story.
Why not?
l mean, not as far as l'm concerned.
The pictures came out pretty well.
Want to have a look at them?
How about a blow-up
from a negative that size?
- Her first cigarette!
- Yeah.
The Mouth of Truth.
l had a caption in mind:
''Barber cuts in.''
Here's the key shot
for the whole layout.
''The Wall Where
Wishes Come True.''
Joe, that's good.
Lead off with that,
then follow up with the wishes?
l got that from the file.
''Princess lnspects Police.''
Yeah...
''Police lnspects Princess.''
- How about that?
- Pretty good.
l got a topper for you.
- Wow!
- ls that a shot?
- What a picture!
''Bodyguard Gets Body Blow.''
No, how about this?
''Crowned Head?'' Huh?
Oh, l get it. Joe, you got...
She's fair game, Joe.
lt's always open season
on princesses.
- You must be out of your mind.
- l know, but...
Look, l can't prevent you from
selling the pictures, if you want to.
- You'll get a good price for them.
- Yeah.
- Are you going to the interview?
- Are you?
Yeah. lt's an assignment, isn't it?
Yeah.
l'll see you.
lt ain't much, but it's home.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please approach.
Her Royal Highness.
Your Royal Highness,
the ladies and gentlemen
of the press.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Her Royal Highness
will now answer your questions.
l believe at the outset,
Your Highness,
that l should express
the pleasure of all of us,
at your recovery
from the recent illness.
Thank you.
Does Your Highness believe
that federation could be a solution
to Europe's economic problems?
l am in favour of any measure
which would lead
to closer cooperation in Europe.
And what, in the opinion
of Your Highness,
is the outlook for
friendship among nations?
l have every faith in it...
...as l have faith
in relations between people.
May l say, speaking for
my own press service...
...we believe that Your Highness's
faith will not be unjustified.
l am so glad to hear you say it.
Which of the cities visited
did Your Highness enjoy the most?
Each in its own way
was unforgettable.
lt would be difficult to...
Rome! By all means, Rome.
l will cherish my visit here
in memory, as long as l live.
Despite your indisposition,
Your Highness?
Despite that.
Photographs may now be taken.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
l would now like to meet some of
the ladies and gentlemen of the press.
Hitchcock, ''Chicago Daily News''.
- l'm so happy to see you here.
- Thank you.
Scanziani, ''La Suisse''.
Klinger, Deutsche Presse Agentur.
Maurice Montabré, ''Le Figaro''.
Sytske Galema,
''De Linie'', Amsterdam.
Jacques Ferrier, ''lci Paris''.
Gross, ''Davar Tel Aviv''.
Cortes Cavanillas, ''ABC Madrid''.
Lampe, ''New York Herald Tribune''.
- Good afternoon.
lrving Radovich, CR Photo Service.
How do you do?
May l present Your Highness
with some commemorative photos
of your visit to Rome?
Thank you so very much.
Joe Bradley, American News Service.
So happy, Mr Bradley.
Moriones, ''La Vanguardia'', Barcelona.
Stephen House, of the
''London Exchange Telegraph''.
Good afternoon.
De Aldisio, Agence Press.